Hello and welcome to the Junkyard Love Podcast.
Hello and welcome, aliens and alienettes and humans and primates and zombies and whatever else
you may be listening to this.
This is the Junkyard Love Podcast, I'm Jake Rines.
And today we've got a wonderful conversation with my wonderful friend, Jay.
It's super awesome.
Can't wait to get to it before real quick.
I'm going to give you a recommendation.
I'd like to give a little recommendation for the podcast, get going.
This week is going to be why good leaders make you feel safe by Simon's Senate.
It's on YouTube.
It's a TED Talk.
It's 12 minutes long.
It's fantastic.
Check it out and enjoy the rest of your day.
Also real quick, before the conversation gets going, breathe out slowly and just be present.
Remember where you're at.
Slow down, let go of your shoulders, relax.
Everything's alright.
All right, enjoy the combo.
I feel like famous.
Today.
I know it feels so official to just have headphones on and you're like, this microphone
is for me.
I gotta talk into it.
No, I like it.
It's nice.
Hello, Jay.
Welcome to the Junkyard Love Podcast.
Hi, thank you.
I feel so honored to actually be here.
Yeah, I feel honored that you would come on and just talk about yourself and share some
cool stuff.
Yeah.
So just because it's right here and we were talking about it briefly, let's just start
with Shocker.
You want to just let's say, let's say that I'm going to told a dummy and I don't know anything
much.
I know a little bit, but I just want to say that I kind of don't, too.
You know, like a little bit.
Yeah, I understand the concept, but because with a lot of the stuff that I learned
about when I do yoga, yoga for me, for example, wasn't like a series of going through
trainings and going to a lot of classes where people taught, it was just kind of like clicking
around through YouTube and like I would stretch and like, okay, my fingers can touch the floor
and it feels good to lift my hand up and these sort of things.
So I love the explanations.
Like when people talk about Shocker, I love that I'm so open to it now.
Yeah.
Well, it's you.
Right.
Yeah, it starts making sense.
It's so funny.
I feel like before I would be very deflective.
I don't know what that is.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't want to hear it.
When you just listen, it's like how to make sense.
Yeah.
Well, it's interesting.
I feel like when you're not ready to hear about it, it's because you're not ready
to heal.
So when you start learning about Shocker, you're ready to start healing them, right?
So I'm not expert by any means, but I actually got them tattooed on my back when I was
18 and I just feel like Shocker is like, oh my gosh.
Makes sense.
So basically there's a bunch, but there's like the seven main ones and their wheels.
So think of them as like spinning wheels.
So if you can imagine that one is blocked and you try to pour water in the top, like
wheels of water and one is blocked, right?
How is it going to get the water going to get down?
It's going to be blocked.
So think about that with energy.
So think people who have like, I start like my throat shocker is like closing up talking
now, but think about like people who can give love, but they can't receive love.
I'm one of those people.
So I'll have back pain in between my shoulder blades.
Like someone's pushing their palm between my blades.
So the shocker in the back is for receiving, which is blocked.
So much of my life where I'm pushing out through my front heart.
I can give love.
But then I'm not receiving any.
So it's like loves going out, but love can't come in.
So it's literally physically causing symptoms in my body.
Right, that tightness.
And that's because my back shocker is open because I can't receive.
But when I'm like, I, it's so easy to open your shockers and that's why I love
them because I can just say, I'm open to receiving love.
And I can just envision like green.
Okay.
And it opens.
So do you, okay, so your back shocker, for example, is that the color that I feel like?
Yeah, so I can go from the beginning.
No, no, you're fine.
We can dance around.
But like, so for this example when you're saying, it's blocked.
Like I feel this pain in my back.
Like can you sit down?
Do you treat this as a meditation or do you just like, so you set aside a couple minutes
and you just get your thoughts like, okay, what is that feeling?
Yeah.
Do you focus on the spot itself?
I do kind of bold.
So it's like, I know I didn't like exercise my back.
So it's like, why does my back hurt?
And I just actually learned in the shocker class that a lot of healers close off their receiving
because they're not good enough or they don't think they should receive, which is something
I struggle with my whole life is receiving is so hard for me.
It's like, what you want to do something nice for me.
I don't deserve that because of that inner child, right?
I don't deserve this because our parents might just feel like that or other people.
So I just what I would do is I would sit and I'll actually have like certain stones for it.
But and I just envision like green and like opening it up.
And I actually think of like a wheel and like opening it up.
And you can like even like move your hand like counterclockwise in front of your heart
to clear the gunk and then you can move your other hand clockwise to put good energy in.
And it's so easy like anyone can do it.
Like you don't have to be a healer.
Yeah, it's funny.
We think of like why would you do that?
And but if you if you just try it, I mean definitely I would definitely agree.
If you just try these things I love following all these just on YouTube like visualizations.
They'll have things if that same manner.
I listed one the other day that it made your all of your shocker as you imagine them as different flowers.
Yeah.
Oh man and just it felt wonderful.
It's just sometimes for me like I'll be like, how do you even realize I was blocked in this area?
I didn't realize I had some tightness in this area and then you do one of those and it seems to help out.
Yeah, so as I was like kind of prepping for today because I feel like shockers are something that anyone and everyone should know about.
So basically there's like seven main ones.
So there's like the rut which is red.
It's like kind of in the lower area and then it goes up to like the sake roll, which is like your sexuality.
It's an orange color and then you go up to your solar which is like your stomach, your womb if you're female.
And then it's like your power center and then you go up to your heart.
It's more green.
It can also be pink.
You go up to your throat.
It's blue.
Go up to your third eye and then your crown.
Right.
So I just thought it was interesting because this is me.
So if you have a like solar plexus imbalance which is like yellow.
You're addicted to food, caffeine, starches, detailed and compulsive cleaning.
So you can see what shockers are blocked in like common addictions.
Right.
And it's like, well, like I'm in love potatoes and coffee and like compulsive cleaning.
Yeah, it's cleaning.
And like my solar and plexus is imbalance and I know that.
And so what do you do?
So you're like, okay, I know I recognize these things like those are totally me.
That's speaking to me.
What's your what's your step there?
Like you're like, okay, do I need to I can't just obviously I'm addicted to these, you know, I want these
Starts you foods.
I want this caffeine.
Like what do you do to help balance those things?
So actually like today I'm having coffee but actually quit drinking coffee because I'm like, I'm not going to let a substance rule.
Right.
When you start, I feel when you have discipline over what you eat, you have discipline over your whole life.
Hmm.
I feel personally.
Food is such like a trigger for so many people.
Like there's a bull M&M's like, who isn't going to try to eat one or who has that discipline
to just sit there and go, no, my body doesn't want that.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I have a shaving iron.
I think I think I think I think we're on day 20 or so of a whole 30 again.
I love that.
Yeah, this is my third time doing it.
And I think that every time I do it, I feel a little tougher.
I feel a little stronger.
I feel a little like, I mean, I feel fantastic just by, you know, not eating.
And apparently I have the podcast.
I've had people come over and we'll go like have a beer afterwards or we'll go, you know, have some food afterwards.
So I was getting carried away with that.
But just resetting and like knowing like me because I can tell like, okay, you know, my,
my stomach's not feeling great, you know, and you could follow it.
You know, why?
Yeah.
So it's good to explore.
And like, all right, I'm going to take a break for me.
And you with caffeine, like, you're like, I, it's not helping me.
It's like a treat sometimes, you know?
Yeah.
It's nice and it's comforting.
And I work at a coffee shop.
I love coffee.
And I think it like bright and seepals day.
But when it's, I need coffee.
That's when it's a problem to me.
I need to eat potatoes tonight.
Like that's where it's like my energies imbalanced because I don't need anything.
But love, right?
But like, so I'm seeing that and I'm recognizing it.
And then it also stems to like, so that's like your power center.
So it's like, I am good enough.
I am enough.
I've been working on that lately too, where I don't like,
I've been like trying to apply to the hospital.
Like, I'm, I have my bachelor's degree in nursing, but I work at a coffee shop.
You know, and it's like this internal, like, I'm not good enough to work in the hospital.
I'm not smart enough. I don't know enough.
And that's that chakra.
Okay.
So it's like, to really just like work on it.
But like, it's really easy to just do all of them.
I have a pendulum and like, moving.
But you can just open it with meditation or with fasting.
I love to fast.
I love to fast water and just cleanse and let your body reset or go out in nature and just reconnect.
Yeah.
But you can heal them really fast.
And a lot of people will have chronic blockages and all physical ailments come from
chakra and balances.
It starts in the orc field,
chakra imbalance, emotional imbalance, physical imbalance.
Okay. So okay. So a lot of nurses get sick.
A lot of doctors get sick.
A lot of healthy people can get sick.
Why I'm so healthy because they're working with sick people.
And that energy is coming into their orc field.
And they don't know how to cleanse it because they're not.
Right.
And they're getting sick.
I think that I think that a lot of our the world we live in is so disconnected from the body.
You know, I mean, where it's something.
So even me, I've always been athletic, I've always worked out.
But I always had, you know, like, my arm looks tight in this shirt.
But like if it gets too tired around my belly, like,
I'm super self conscious about it.
These sort of things.
But like, and now, you know, I do yoga and I don't really care about how I look.
It's about how I feel.
And it's this like this shift.
I feel like when you're so obsessed about how you look,
you're almost like, you know, say, say, you, you know, have a belly right now.
You're like, oh, I've been eating too much or whatever.
The disc content, the non-connected feelings that you send that area of your body.
Well, the thing is to the more when I'm focused on how overweight I am,
I'm going to stay overweight because that's what I'm telling my body.
Right.
If I look at my body and I say, thank you for food.
I'm glad I'm full.
Right.
Because some people are starving.
So instead of looking at your body as like discussed and oh, I'm overweight,
how about you say, I have the best body.
I have a six pack or I can run.
I'm healthy.
I can breathe like so many people can't walk.
So many people can't even feed themselves.
So many people don't have food.
So shift that mindset to being like, wow, thank you.
Maybe I have a belly, but at least I'm not starving.
And to kind of just shift your body.
I don't want to be the one who would love to have that.
Yeah.
Right.
Like shift your mindset and be like, maybe this isn't where I want to be at.
But envision yourself like, oh, I really want to like, I'm overweight.
Like I swear like every time I'm in that mindset, I stay overweight.
Even if I'm working out eating good and like I'm not losing weight.
Because you're saying that.
Right.
You are your commander.
Like your body follows and like your subconscious doesn't know like the difference.
Yeah.
You got to train your subconscious.
I always say that.
So conscious is running things 95% of the time.
Yeah.
And like when you find that 5% we have it.
But when you can find that we're like, okay, I'm noticing that I'm running on autopilot.
Then it can insert these other thoughts in there.
And so instead of if you're feeling these feelings of shameless or like, oh, I'm overweight or I'm this and you can't seem to like connect with what does this have to do with other people.
Just I think just stop and think of the benefit of the way that you're thinking.
Like it does this lead you to healing.
Does it lead you to feeling better?
A lot of times we feel something and we think we have to just feel it forever.
Like that's me.
I have this overweight sad feeling in my belly and that's me forever.
That's just who I am.
And then anybody who tries to come at it, you just stop them with your soared and they you know you protect yourself from it.
We all have those things.
Yeah.
Well, Jay, I definitely want to talk about, well, actually let's back up your name.
Even we were talking about your name.
You're going to be Jay.
I know, but I have said it a couple of times.
Let's get your your full name that you have like to be called now that you've grown older.
My full name is actually Jordan now.
Okay.
I feel we're kind of talking about this earlier, but I feel like I like grew into my name.
You know, I didn't start really start using it until I went to college and I was rushing from my sorority and it was printed right there.
I'm like, I can't hide it now.
Right.
It's there.
And then a lot of times people like don't want to call me I go, is there anything?
Well, it's too long or it's the little and it's like, yeah, call me Jay.
I don't know, it just started happening when I was little and then our jordy, your Jordan or
Amjol, whatever name, like I'm like call me whatever, because some people were like, you know, when people get starbucks drinks and they spell their name wrong, they're so offended.
That's so weird.
Isn't it?
I'm like, why does it bother you so much?
It's like a trigger.
That's as way out.
People love us picture by all the times, like first of all, they're stressed.
Like, is it really a big deal that they spell your name wrong?
Like, that's what they're thinking about and that's what you're so certain.
I mean, yeah.
But we have this weird thing with our name.
Like, if someone call me the wrong name, I don't correct.
Like, I'm like, but I'm very passive.
Like, whatever.
Like, I'll let someone call me the wrong name for a long time.
Like, I really am so passive.
I'm like, I just hate conflict so much that I'm like, it's fine.
But other people are like, no, my name.
I'm really like into their power though, and I used to get mad at those people.
But I was mad because there's a trigger because I wasn't like that.
Because you weren't standing up for yourself.
Yeah.
Because it's like, you know, when you are upset, I always talk with it.
Like, on my personal Instagram, like, if someone is doing something and it bothers you,
there's a reason for that.
And that shit's going to keep happening until it doesn't bother you anymore.
Right.
Because eventually, that's the same stuff going to happen.
And you're not even noticing it because it doesn't bother you.
Once you work on your triggers, they just, there's less.
Well, you notice that you don't really care what other people are doing.
No.
And people don't care what you're doing.
Yeah.
We always talk about that.
A good example.
Like, say you take the garbage out to the curb, right?
And you're like, you're in your pajama pants and sandals.
And you're like, oh, man, my neighbors are going to think that I'm a total scrub.
It's like, your neighbors don't even know you exist right now.
They don't care what you're like.
That guy is putting his garbage out to the curb.
If they even think that, they probably will literally just see it.
And not even let the full fuck come into their mind.
They're so not caring about what you're doing.
I feel that.
Like, you know, I'm like the crazy, I'm like going out full moon,
like collecting rainwater and cleansing my rocks.
And my people of my partners like no one cares what you're doing.
They might be looking at you because they're curious,
but they're not like no one cares what you're doing.
Yeah.
They're like, like, go.
I love that.
That's great.
I mean, that's, you know, I'm happy to have you on this podcast because
you know, that's, that's my whole thing here is that everybody has something to teach you.
Knowledge is power like in just being open to like, hey, like what,
like what do you think about this whole thing we've got going on?
You know, like, because, you know, a lot of us have read the same,
the same books in school and we've been raised in the same areas.
And so there's a lot of stuff that we know similar, right?
And we do find things that are different about each other and we kind of poke at them.
Because we're, we're in a couple, but I don't like that.
I like finding things that are different.
I think it's kind of different.
Right.
And yeah, I just like finding things about people, like, oh, I don't know,
I just being so open to new experiences in, in new ways of thinking about life
because when you're open to it, it seems like it's like, oh,
my life is now improving in this way or if something isn't working out for you,
maybe there's a belief around that that you have that could be like changed.
You know, you don't, I think just, just,
allowing people to, to open up and be themselves.
Yeah, I'll send it.
Yeah, and because I, like I said, I, you know, I have a lot of,
last couple years, the spirituality thing is new for me.
And so like I said, I was telling you, like, I find myself going to your Instagram.
I'm like, oh, it's great because these are things that like,
I'm like, I don't know, I don't know about that,
but it seems like it kind of makes sense to me.
And it feels right in the experience of this thing.
Yeah, definitely resonates with me.
And then so having these things where you can kind of get answers or feel like there's someone else who's connecting with you.
That's what it's all about.
I think just realizing everybody has a different way of seeing things,
but there's so many similarities and there's so many ways that like,
you don't have to stay at the same.
You could be like, hey, like, like, like, Jordan else,
other thing than like, it was just profound to me.
I've never even thought about it before, but now like,
I'm gonna try that shit tomorrow.
You know?
Yeah.
This world is for, I think, and I think it's very healing to learn and just try new things.
I think, like, for me, I've always just kind of,
I mean, I've always really been comfortable.
Like, I've never been the girl that we're makeup,
not against wearing makeup at all, but I've always just been me.
Like, I can wake up and go.
Like, because I am who I am.
You know what I mean?
And I feel like so many of us are like,
just scared to show up for ourselves,
scared to look in the mirror.
You know, like, how, like, why can't you?
Like, who's making you feel less than?
It's yourself and like, why can't you just like be authentic for you?
And I'm telling you when you're authentic for you,
your life just, just, just, just, just, just.
The right door is open because what I was doing is I'm such a people-pleaser.
I don't need me.
So like, I remember this coffee shop this guy's a hunter.
And he's like, want to see what I killed.
And I'm like, being passive.
I'm like, yeah, but no, but no, I don't.
Okay.
But do you know what I mean?
It's like, when you engage in conversations that you don't like,
you are creating false energy cords with these people
and false attachments.
And I just heard the other day,
it's better to be respected than loved, which is huge for me.
I like that.
Because I am so, like, yes, like, yes, like,
like, like, I just want everyone to become real and happy,
but it's like, you need to say no.
No is so powerful.
And that's like, my biggest lesson is like,
no, I don't want to do that.
And I don't need to explain myself.
Yeah, when it comes to self-love,
you know, that's such a bust feed word at this point.
You know, so no, it's your little confusing.
What does that mean?
Yeah.
There's a million different, you know, what does it mean to you is what it is?
But a lot of saying no is self-love.
Seriously.
And like, you know, when you start,
just like a history,
I've been on my spiritual journey for about 11 years.
I started really meditating and diving into it about five years ago.
But I wanted to come on here and say that you don't just wake up in one day.
And you don't just wake up in your happy,
like, it's been a lot of shadow self and a lot of dark days.
It's not all incense and crystals and, like,
love yourself.
Like, it's really not all like that.
Like, yeah, I'm like that on my Instagram
because that's how I want my followers to be encouraged.
But I also want them to know that, like,
and who's listening that it doesn't happen overnight
and it, it's work.
Because you have to dig deep and, like,
see your childhood self and, like,
outside influences and, like, heal.
But when you start healing your memories,
it actually relires the future.
Because you can change your, like, a bad experience.
Look at it in a different way.
Yeah.
You can look at it.
Instead of experiencing it as the sufferer that you were,
you can look at it from the witness perspective of a 20-something-year-old person
who's like, okay, this thing happened to me.
What about it?
Like, let's look at it.
What really happened and what's different.
Now, how can I perceive it differently than my childhood self did?
Yeah.
And, like, how are no people of heal?
This is, like, I'm like, dig into your trauma as a child.
If they can't even talk, they start to feel like,
they're throat shock-root.
They have not done the work.
Right.
Like, when I first started opening up about, like, my childhood,
because I had, like, to me, I had a traumatic childhood,
but now I don't see it like that.
But if I were to tell you my story, you'd be like,
how are you, how are you this way?
Which didn't have anything.
So, I think it's really important to just realize that,
also, like, don't, I talk with us, don't compare trauma.
Like, I see people doing that.
We're like, okay, let's go.
I don't compare trauma.
Like, I see people doing that.
We're like, well, this happened to me.
So, I should be more messed up.
Or, like, this didn't happen to you.
You've had a great life.
Well, you don't know how they perceived it.
Like, this is because they had two parents, and they had money.
Doesn't mean that they had a great life as individual.
And it's so important to know, because we often compare, like,
oh, I didn't have a parent.
Or, my parents died.
Or, like, there's so much, like, comparing our lives
to, like, justify how we act, but just own up to, like, it.
Yeah, yeah, it doesn't make sense to compare because it's, like, I've used this example before, like,
you could be terrified of snakes today because when you were six,
not you got bit by snake, but a man who was wearing a snake shirt,
yelled at you.
Yeah.
I mean, like, that's, you know, that's a short extension of the word
childhood trauma.
But I feel like we do hear words sentences like childhood trauma.
Very often, and it's when you start learning more about it,
there's so much to it.
Well, like, the ace is right.
Have you heard of the ace is right?
The ten questions?
Oh, no, hit me with him.
Do you remember?
I don't know them all off hand, but it's, like, a parent's in a jail.
Um, you've been, like, sexually assaulted.
One of your more parents was a substance abuser.
Um, this, like, all the things that, like,
things that, like, trauma.
And it actually, I'm, I'm 10 out of 10, by the way, which is, like, the highest, where you can get.
Yes.
And I'm predicted to not go to school and predict, like, in it's crazy,
because it's showing that trauma can change your DNA in this lifetime.
They're literally seeing at a molecular level that these trauma is changing your DNA,
and also trauma is passed down.
Mm-hmm.
And we are the generation to heal that ancestral trauma and stop it.
I absolutely believe that, too.
No more of it.
We are not our grandparents.
Yeah.
We are not our parents, even.
There's a, you know, in a jumping to, like, culture society.
Sometimes I feel like right now, you know, a lot of a, a lot of our job, like, my job, for example, like, I'm, I'm a, I'm a good moderator.
I would say I'm good at having two different types of people in, in, we can have a conversation that all, you know, all three of us.
I enjoy that.
Um, a lot of times I feel like, I just, I just, I just see this and feel this huge disconnect between, like,
our age and older generations.
Yes.
There's like, we had us.
Yeah.
Very much so, but, but I think a lot of what it is is we're, like, uh, you, so think about hearing as a parent,
think about hearing words like childhood trauma.
Um, they instantly take that on themselves, like, oh, I was a terrible parent, or whatever.
I had a little trouble with my own mother, um, because we're, so, like, because I'm in the, I'm, I'm coco, I'm in, in the cocoon a little bit now.
I'm through my hero's journey.
I'm not through, I'm in the middle of my hero's journey.
I'm still, um, I still, you know, my throat still closes up when I talk about, I'm still trying to deal with a lot of things.
Right.
And then things wrong with that either.
No, no, yeah, but, but I, yeah, I think, for saying that I think that talking about it and getting it like, I am in the middle of it.
I'm not claiming to not be on the other side of things, but I'm not ignoring it.
That's for sure.
But I think a lot of the, the disconnect is so much of like, a lot of, it's almost like older people take it as offensive.
Like we're saying, oh, you're, you were terrible parents and you, we didn't, it's like,
no, it's, that's not what's happening.
Like when we, when we say words like, childhood trauma or like, uh, this thing happened to you when you are younger thing.
And now you have to have this, a dog relationship with parents.
You can see the best parents in your kids still has childhood trauma.
Absolutely.
But you know what I've learned is parents do the best with what they have.
Mm-hmm.
And I bet you their parents weren't any better.
Right.
At least from my family.
I see my, I live with my grandma and my mom.
I live on the second parcel.
And I see it like the trauma in my grandma is just so alive.
Like she would die without it.
If you like healed her trauma, she would die.
She would send because that's her.
She needs it to live.
Like she always talks about how poor she was and all this.
And like it is her.
She cannot move forward and depression is living in the past.
Insighty living in the future.
She doesn't have anxiety.
She has, she has someone's eye with it.
It's so like trauma.
Like these people back in my day.
Like they need it.
Right.
But us, it's like, I don't, it's a part of me and I appreciate it.
Because it's brought me here.
But I want to like move forward.
Yeah.
Like I know some of my whole identity.
But I have those older generation.
It is a lot of them.
And like to tell them to heal like who are you like, no.
Right.
Like, you know, they didn't go to counseling.
They didn't have the tools that we do now.
They didn't have the internet.
Like they weren't meditating.
They weren't thinking about it in a healthy way.
Right.
Like we are really pushed to do that.
I feel like our generation pushed to do that.
I mean, especially like, you know, people, like I imagine, I spend a crazy amount of time on YouTube and learning about these things.
I don't, do you spend a good amount of time?
Yeah.
I mean, it's, but what it is is, you know, I'm not watching, you know, Parks and Rec for the fifth time on YouTube.
I'm, which I would love to.
But I, you know, I'm like learning these things.
Like, our parents just simply or older people simply didn't have access to what we do.
These things.
I mean, so if I wanted to go, okay, what is what is meditation?
What is booties and what is any of these things that if I wanted to know this information 30 years ago, I would have to travel to India, talk to the right person, travel to travel.
Yeah.
Like, find the shaman.
It's six months in India.
And then eight months here.
So every year.
Yeah.
All these things.
But nowadays, all of those people, 30 years ago, who were doing that, like people who I listened to every day, they come back now and they have conversations about what they learned.
And so people like you and I get to listen to that information.
So instead of, so not that I'm saying like where that I have the knowledge of a monk, we'll travel to the top of the mountains.
But there is, you know, we have some things that are helpful for people to learn.
And yeah, when you are knowledge, the internet has made it to where we know so much.
The sentence we know more than our parents doesn't, that doesn't make sense.
That's not what I'm trying to say.
Right.
But you're more aware.
Yeah, our, our knowledge base and the details of, like, you know,
further towards truth and further towards not ignoring our feelings, our inner, our spirit, not ignoring that stuff.
We're figuring that out.
And we're able to, we're getting slower slowly.
We're starting to put things into words more and more.
I think.
I feel like a lot of people listening, you're probably told a young age to shut up.
Or don't say that.
Be quiet in public.
You know, don't talk about that.
And that blocks your throat and that blocks your creativity and, like, little kids are just open the imagination.
Like, that, you know, they're so excited.
Like, to me, telling a kid to shut up.
I know it's like, I'm not a parent, so I can't do it.
But it, like, and every time you're telling them to shut up, it's like,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
And then they just get in this box where they don't talk.
Yeah.
Or they don't talk about anything meaningful.
And they don't look, and they don't talk from within.
They talk from without, if that makes sense.
No, it does.
So I actually, when I was like nine, my, my life started getting just, like, super hectic.
And it was essentially this, what I felt was anything you have to say is adding to the,
the problematic situation that is your life.
So it was very, like, it was very suppressed what I really would want to say.
And then so it's kind of, you know, you get older and you don't realize that you have suppressed these sort of things.
And a lot of, like, our personality traits are, like, trying to fit in with different situations.
When we're just, when the real last, it's a way to survive in your dream.
Yeah.
As a child.
And like the way I was like thinking today, I was like, how did I survive when trauma being overly kind and nice?
Because no one questions the kind person, no one thinks that their mom's using math and the bathroom, right?
No one thinks that this kind, little girl has a fucked up life at home.
Right.
You know what I mean, I had some teachers be like, well, you go, okay, but like, no one questions the kids who are acting out.
They're acting out.
But just being so kind, to kill them with kindness.
And I always talk about them.
So no one's asking me about Jay.
No one's asking about Jordan now.
It's always them talking to me.
So I don't have that opportunity or I don't allow people to ask me how I'm doing because I was doing horrible, right?
Right.
So it's always opening to listening to my friends and little bit.
I was never really talking about me until recently.
But like, I was always about them or other people.
And that was just a defense mechanism because I wasn't doing good.
Do you know what I mean?
I had a lot of trauma.
I was angry inside.
Like, if you saw me in my house, way different from like how you saw me at school.
Yeah, because if you talk about it, that means you got to face it as the thing.
Yeah.
So that's, it's more embarrassed or like, you don't want to like, you know, it's her.
You don't want to talk about your her or what hurt you and do you ever feel sometimes?
I feel like we share amongst our individual friend groups,
growing up like all, you know, inevitably we're the person who people text like, hey, I've got the thing going on.
And I love it.
Like it's what I live for.
I love helping people and you know, responding with like, they trust my opinion.
Like I can be straight up with my friends and they want to hear it, you know.
Do you ever, we were talking about before this about like,
taking a lot of that, taking it on, but not not exactly like draining it, right?
And so you want to go on a little bit.
What are some ways that you drain these things?
Like, not that like your friends give you problems and you got to just like, get them away.
But there is a lot of like, we accidentally hold on to things that aren't ours.
Yeah.
And there's a lot of me personally.
You talk about nature.
I'm huge into nature.
This was well for this reason.
For the first thing is real.
Yeah.
For the first thing.
Yeah, I go on to become like a forest by their friendship.
Well, that's like an epic term.
Okay. Okay.
So it's crazy because like, I'm Japanese, right?
So forest bathing is like a Japanese technique in what they're doing with these depressed
patients is they're just going out with them in the forest and they're literally doing brain scans
and they're carrying depression and anxiety with the forest.
Fantastic.
So the reason we love, and that's a big part of my Instagram too, is like, get outside.
Like you guys are sad.
Go outside and connect because we're disconnected because you know what we do.
We wake up in a box.
We get and put our food in a box.
We get in a box and we drive to a box.
We leave the box, get in the box.
If anybody threatens our box, we attack it.
We attack their box.
And you stay in this box and you're a cyclical human beings and you're in the box and you're
in the box and you're in the box and it's like, oh yeah, hiking like, oh, they're it's a
fat.
No, it's not.
It's more than to me than hiking.
Right.
It's get outside because nature is just waiting to heal you.
Yeah.
It is just way, like I'm getting chills talking about it because that's why I'm here.
So like nature is like, it's perfect.
Right.
You don't even have to do anything and it's just growing.
You didn't plant that tree.
Who planted that tree?
No one knows.
Isn't it just fast?
See, I love doing that.
So because I'm, you know, sometimes it's great to turn off my thinking.
Right.
But sometimes I like going into nature and just letting it rip as in like, oh, like,
God, like how old could that tree possibly?
Oh, my, how did this link get here?
Just letting yourself be this like, wondrous explorer.
You are the same front of you.
You are the tree.
That's like my meditation is, um, you are that it is in you.
So what I do is I'll go outside barefoot.
I'll collect things and I just sit and I usually do this alone and I sit and you all around you is in you.
You are everything and when you can be like that and sit because if the God particle right.
So if you look at everything in a molecular level, it's the same little Buddha guy.
It's called the God particle.
So that's where I like God is everywhere.
It's not God up in the cloud with this beard and the button.
No thing against Bible or anything but to me God is everywhere.
I see God everywhere I look because someone like nature is like how I connect.
Like I'm like a toning day and I'm like my religion is nature.
Like if we went out and like worship like the trees and stuff, the world, but just
and just be more like it's so easy to around you and your house is made from nature.
Like do not see that like your wood table is a tree.
Like everything around you is created from nature.
The element and I think we just get like lose connection and I think a lot of depression is a lot that lack of feeling connected.
But if you just go outside and like you don't have to do anything.
You don't have to get somewhere like a lot of people want to hike to the top or
and I love that too but I go to the same spot a lot and I just sit and I look at for something new.
I'm not even looking. I'm just seeing something new.
Yes, yes.
Because the universe is showing me new things because I'm taking the time from my soul.
And when you spend time with your soul you learn more and more and more and more.
But the more I learn the more I realize that I am nature.
Like I am you. Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, do you think I'm going to eat but sorry?
No, that's wonderfully deep. I love it. Keep going deeper.
It's great. Sometimes I feel that my so me for example, you know, I categorize myself with ADHD a lot.
I do that though. I'm always very weary of like I don't like categorizing myself because I don't want to feel like I'm a victim of it.
Or like I'm I'm penciling myself in in my hands.
Well, that's the ego struggle.
Yeah, right.
ego likes labels.
Definitely does.
But I find that something that I didn't realize that I wasn't ever being able to turn off before I started going into
outside by myself more again.
Last couple years, I like this task, this task mind where it's like you need to do something at all times.
You're always assigning yourself a task and completing it.
And if you're not in the middle of it, you actually have this panic.
You're like, I don't have a task right now. I'm going to grab my phone.
I'm going to do something. I'm going to take a picture.
I'm going to whatever.
But like when you're outside if you give yourself a few hours and you realize like, I don't have to have it.
The task doesn't have to be the end.
It could be this in between.
Like me, I really, what I have, what I have success with is while I'm outside getting myself away from my current thoughts and my current spot life as I think about my life.
Zoom out, zoom way out.
When I'm on my deathbed versus when I was born, what do I want to be?
Like if I'm looking at my life as a timeline, like the little things are right now.
Like what do I want to like, okay, I want hiking, like I experienced hiking for this many hours.
Like you know, see it as something before I die.
I want to have experienced this.
I want to fuel the outdoors.
So like when you say timeline, so time isn't linear for those of you listening.
The past and the future are happening right now.
I think of time as a record player.
So it's crazy.
So like when talking back about changing your perception on your childhood memories, you change your future.
And they're saying so many times you can meditate and you heal.
And you start to forget memories that you held onto.
And I feel like memories are almost keys.
But like, I'll forget things so easily, because I don't need to remember it anymore.
It's not who I am.
Does that make sense?
But when you're talking about this timeline and these things, so your future is happening right now.
Like everything.
So it's not a linear.
It's totally all right now.
Like the world creating beginning, like dinosaur, like it's all here happening right now.
And that is so important to realize that you can change right now.
Like your thought one thought can change your whole future.
One interaction.
I'm at my partner and I knew right away and I went for it.
What if I wasn't third that night?
You know, so it's like, but everything led you up to right here right now in this moment.
But it's all happening right now.
If that makes sense.
I think of time like, and I know it's super crazy, but it's like,
Oh, it does.
It's profound though.
That's that's how I see it.
I don't, I was meditating one day and I was like,
because we get so stuck with right, at least I'm always in the future.
Let's something I need to work on, but like,
it was like, oh, but like when you're envisioning yourself and when you're feeling psychic,
I almost feel like I'm tapping in to the future and I'm getting like a glimpse of it.
It's not like I'm even like visioning or manifesting.
It's almost like, like I'm like dipping into the future.
You saw a little bit of like someone showed you a little bit.
Yeah, it's like a block.
Yeah.
So it's like now the universe grants me the vision of me owning an herbal shop.
Now what that's what I want to do and what can I do to get there.
So when you see these memories or visions of your future,
go for it because it's showing you it for a reason.
My mom always says, and I had a dream.
I was like on a podium and I'm like,
what didn't have a dream if you couldn't do it or you wouldn't have that dream in the first place?
If that makes sense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like you want to do this.
I want to do that.
It's all aren't too big.
It's our sole guidance.
You can't with a lot of if you don't buy a lot or take it right.
100%.
But like this day's connect.
So when I get sad, it's because I'm not aligned with my sole's higher purpose.
And a lot of people, I don't know what I want to do.
But with a, and my big, what spirit tells me is do it brings you joy.
For me being in my garden planting plants.
Yeah.
Joy, that's it. You're doing it.
You don't have to like do all these crazy things.
Of course you can, but like joy, you can't like,
like, joy is it. That's all you need.
Right.
It's so simple.
We over-complicate it.
There we go.
You go to these foreign countries that have nothing in our eyes.
They're happy.
I know we have more, we add more, so we add more problems.
Yeah.
You need to simplify and analyze.
I'm not going to be in my tiny house.
I have not been like more happy.
I don't have walls.
I don't have power.
I don't have water.
I don't have toilet.
I play with it.
Okay. Let's talk about your tiny house.
Because it's so sick to me.
I saw a couple of things.
You had a couple of videos.
And then we were talking about your telling me like a little bit of the size.
Yeah.
I was like wondering, I don't know.
I don't think that I'm the type of person who can do it at this point.
I don't think that we have it.
But it's for everyone.
Yeah.
But it's so cool that it's that it's for you.
And I want to hear about it.
I'm living with another person in there.
Oh yeah.
So from conceptualization when you first had the thought or saw like a tiny house start there.
This is, so I don't know like how long but I've always loved like your and little hobbit houses and like,
you know, it just feels cozy to me.
Like it's crazy how you have the smallest.
So I'm a tourist.
So I love home and I love making people feel comfortable.
Sometimes I feel like you're in a big space.
It's almost harder to do that.
You're hanging all in.
So my house is 24 by 20 and I envision like having tea parties and like get together
and people are just so comfortable with themselves because like when you're in a small space,
like you have to just be, you're, this is it.
This is the room.
Like you can't like walk a part of the conversation.
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you're a partying.
Like I'm always in the kitchen talking to random people.
Right.
Because I can't be like the main area.
But when you're like forced to be in one room together, you really just have to show up.
Absolutely.
And like with my tiny house, like I don't even use all of it.
And it's tiny.
So it's like crazy.
I like even I have a small space.
I'm still not using all of the space.
Right.
So it's 24 by 20.
Randomly.
Like it's crazy.
How it all just like aligned my lease was up and my apartment.
And my mom just bought a house and it had a second parcel.
And she wanted to build a house there.
And I'm like, I don't want to spend like 1500 on rent.
Like that's just, I don't really want to afford.
Like I just, this is not me.
I just, I don't know.
I don't like the idea of renting to never own.
Hmm.
Kind of felt like I was like throwing my money away.
Yeah.
Well you have different future plans than we were.
A lot of people are like, you need a buy house right now.
I was like, well, I don't want to own house.
Yeah.
Never meet.
So my house is $6,000 total.
I'm my mom bought it for me.
And I'm paying rent.
But it is just like, again, I don't have walls or water.
Or, but I live on my mom has her main house.
So I go up there to use like the kitchen.
We will have that.
We're just like working on getting electricity.
It's so comfortable.
It's so cozy.
And like, it's me, my boyfriend and our two cats.
And like the cats love it.
And our beds up top.
I love sleeping up top.
Oh yeah.
And like, it's like a loft, like a.
Yeah.
Like you can't like stand up up there.
But like you could like sit up and bed and read.
I can't.
And I partner can't.
But like, it's just, and then there's a loft on the other side.
For like, we're going to do like a little meditation and like room.
Because it's like completely black.
So would you like pillow?
Yeah.
We're going to like pillows and like posters and like black it out.
Because like I like to meditate in the black.
And like that's like, there's all of places you can just get like.
Blackness.
Yeah, but like dark all the time.
So like I'll wake up and I'll eventually go over there.
And I'll just be like dark and like meditate.
And then I envision myself having like an herbal business like ran out of it.
And like I have a garden already and just people can come and like,
I want like a you pick flower place.
And I just want to like bring a little like.
I don't know just energy to the town and like neighborhood
and just how people come connect.
Right.
You know, with like nature in like a different way.
I think that's great.
And I think that it'll definitely shine through like people.
I can totally envision that people leading you and like just come to my tiny house.
It would be such a great full on experience.
You know, we forget a lot of times when we're when we're eating dinner.
You know, we're like, oh, this is so good.
But like we forget about the process of going to the store.
We forget the process of cutting it and washing it and all these things.
And when you can add like they could see like your cheerful face and you tell them a little bit about what
they're what they're taking home or not not just eating wise, but that's great.
Yeah, I think adding to the experience of them coming up to your house.
Let's see, like, I want to do like a you pick herbal place.
So you're really connected to your medicine.
It's not like, oh, I'm buying like St. John's work for my depression.
It's like, no, you're picking it in your dry and I'll dry it for you.
And you can go home with the over making teas for yourself.
And so what I envision is like we're very intuitive and we're very like you see something in your body.
Like, oh, I want that. I don't even know what that herb is, but I'm attracted to it.
Well, you probably need it.
But we don't ever get to see our medicine like that.
So I feel like we can't heal ourselves because we aren't ever given the opportunity to look at our medicine in the face.
So that's why I want to do like a you pick herbal place and you pick garden.
So where it's like, what just walk in the garden with you and meditate and just talk and pick out three herbs that you're drawn to.
I'm not going to tell you what they are. You know, you just, I will, if you ask, but like you just see what you're drawn to.
And then you pick it and you need that because who picked that right?
I like that. So it's like there's not a lot of, I haven't found a place that's like there's one place in Portland that's kind of like that, but I just wanted to like, more on a small scale.
But it's connected people to the medicine.
And you can kind of serve the whole world with it.
No.
Because big corporation or anything.
A lot of times people think that growth is the only, I'm going to growth mindset person.
But sometimes like giant growth isn't always what we're going for.
Yeah.
And what we're going to do here is to make it to where people can come here and pick with their intuition and you can help them with that.
Yeah. And I mean, I do want like a wellness center.
That's something that I've envisioned for 10 years.
I've drawn it up. I've seen it.
But that is like a 20-year plan.
There's your plan.
That's not something.
But it's my main driving force to everything I do is to create this wellness center for people to really come and heal.
Like, heal the soul.
Okay. So yeah, heal the soul. That's what you mean when you say wellness center.
What do you, because your, let's expand a little bit more about you who are.
Yeah.
I feel like, because that's like who you are.
That's who I, yeah.
Yeah.
Like what it, right?
I think so.
It seems like, right?
What do you, what do you feel as like you are?
Like if it's like, okay, I have a duty, a calling.
Like, here's how I help people.
Like what will this center?
Yeah.
I think I, I see it.
I feel it.
I act as if it's already here.
You know, because I see it so vividly.
It's just, it is, but it is like,
like, calm you and like living together, something that I crave.
I'm an American like, I crave missing.
Like living side by side with people and like sharing and bartering and like growing our own.
Like what I envision, like, I, I, I don't know if I want kids,
I, when I do see my child, it's at this wellness center.
Like living like this lifestyle, because that's the kind of life I want to create for the future is like,
you don't have to live here, but like a place to come and just be.
You don't have to know who you are, your ego, whatever.
Like let's grow vegetables together, like, and pick your food and let's prepare it together and eat like family style and like,
really be connected to the earth and like let's meditate together and like just live in harmony with the earth.
Have you, you know? I love that. I, I, I kind of think about like a meditation retreat center.
Yeah, exactly. I, like, hear, I think, so I work with musicians and artists and stuff.
And so for example, I had a videoographer homey over two nights ago.
And we were talking about, like, he was just saying like, oh, I can so caught up with these things.
We're just talking like, I have so many friends. I hang out with all of them and like, I love hanging out with them,
but I have this trip, and it seems like there's no time to like, you just always have a plan and you're doing doing.
And we were talking about and I have plans with some other musicians of doing like a riding retreat here.
Where it's just like three days, where it's just like, you know, leave your phone upstairs if you can or even maybe don't have to.
But, um, and just connect to like the structure of of not like working, working, working, but like just like, we're going to write, if it comes up.
Yeah, like sit in the backyard and a hammock and write like not we need to start a timer and like get this done in an hour.
Like, you know, that you explore what's happening.
I know, right? Yeah.
Not riding from the soul. It's like ego.
Oh, yes. Like a swore.
Yeah.
Do you write a lot? Do you?
Okay. I know that you write your your captions on Instagram are great. You write their dear right.
Pen and paper too.
Yeah. And it's crazy because I don't read what I write.
I do that.
Do you that? Do you that?
And like, I probably won't listen to this podcast.
You know, um, not not like myself. I listen to your podcast, but like this, like, how dare you?
What who's again, the office, the main guy?
The Steve Grave.
He never watches his TV shows.
The only time he's seen him or his if his kids are watching him.
But I feel that.
I don't know why I don't it's almost like it's not me, but it is me.
But it's like, you know, it's, I don't overanalyze it or like, oh, I should say that or why they say that or I like pick at it.
You know, like a control freak.
I get that you know, okay. So because that's come up a lot, like doing this podcast because I'm friends with most of the people or besides a few of them.
So far, I've been prior friends with them. And so it's an open contact and they're like, oh, I hate my voice or like, please don't show me or make my voice up.
But it's, uh, but people like love my voice. That's the thing.
It's like, I hate it. I think I sound like a little kid.
And it's like two eye pitch and then we're like, my part like I love your voice.
It's sweet.
I can hear you from all the way.
But we're all, that's here.
You know what I mean?
But we're all in our own head cavities thinking that it sounds so strange.
But it's, a lot of the times, uh, Alan Watts, he says this, he says this thing that always sticks to me.
We, uh, somehow an event is ruined if we don't get a good picture of it, you know.
And sometimes it's like, we do feel the need to, you know, I find it's all tick a Snapchat and then I rewatch it before I post it.
Those sort of things if I do that.
I always think like, okay, can I rewind time and make that better or whatever?
And it's, you never can.
It's much as we think we want to.
I feel, you know.
Uh, but it's, you, you just are who you are in this moment and always improving.
I guess you don't really care to like, I mean, I do like, sometimes when I'm writing,
it's, um, sometimes I get overwhelmed with all the thoughts that I have, right?
And I just get consumed.
And then sometimes I get like, well, I'm not here yet, right?
So sometimes when I read all my goals or things that I want to do,
I read like my goals all the time and like I'm a advocate, like,
I'm law of affirmation and planners and mantras and like, I am enough.
I am enough.
I will write the same thing.
100, like crazy, like, oh, it's a right, like, no, like, because like, you need to,
you need to tell yourself, you need to be reminded, like, I'll write on my mirrors.
Like, because I usually don't like to look in the mirror, but it's like, no, I need to show up for myself and look at myself and realize that I am enough.
And everyone that's listening is enough. And I don't think that we tell each other that enough.
I tell my partner every day you are enough. I love you for you.
And we don't, I just got chills saying that to myself, like, we don't tell ourselves, like,
like, our part, like, the real things. You know, oh, yeah, I love you.
I love you. I love you.
Yeah, we say it.
I love you.
We say it. Like, the word you have to say.
But, like, look, you're partner in the eyes and like, me and it and tell them, because you don't know what they're going through.
And we, we've talked about that. Like, you're with somebody and you don't even know what they're feeling.
How often do you think that happened?
We just hide it because we're ashamed of our feelings.
That's right.
No, like talk about it. I'm, I'm adri-kiver-tagant with my feelings.
I probably talk about them too much.
But I have so many that I'm like, let's talk about it.
I need to dissect it.
Yeah, you don't understand it. I mean, yeah, you're trying to understand what's coming out.
And you're trying to allow other people to understand it too.
Yeah.
A lot of times we keep things inside. And, you know, with writing, I don't even know what I think.
Sometimes it's on writing.
I'm like, oh, that's what I think.
Okay, I don't know.
I don't know.
Same, you know.
I feel that.
Put your words, give yourself a place to put the words, so they start to come together.
Like, the past three days that actually had like a little bit of a block, which I never usually get.
Like, you know, the writer's block or whatever.
I'm like, what's happening?
And I think it's just happening because sometimes, like, I get so much, like,
just hyperspinning that I think sometimes I just seem to like chill and not always be with, like,
spirit and divine and like sometimes I just need to be human and just be present because I'm chronically hearing, like, things,
not like bad things, but like,
I think that's on this.
Here's a great idea.
You can do this.
Here's this follows into it.
Funnel, a funnel funnel funnel or like, oh my gosh, like, really look at the, but sometimes I just need to be, like,
shut off.
So I can just like reset and recharge, right?
Because we're a batteries if you think about it.
So if you're draining it and you're putting it out there and you're putting out there and something I also started thinking about was
how many people are like seeing me and how much energy and what kind of energy is going on to people.
Like when they're seeing my stuff and my, because I'm triggering people, I can feel that.
I can feel I'm triggering people and that energy even though we're not physically with them.
It's attached.
Do you know what I mean?
And I'm here to trigger people because I'm waking people up.
I'm expanding on the word triggering because I think that political, political stuff has everyone, where it's like triggering.
I'm not political, but yeah.
But it's, I feel like when I hear that, I hear that.
You're thinking of political.
Okay.
So sometimes like, for example, I'm pretty happy that make someone upset because they're not happy.
Or I'm honest, and that makes someone unhappy because they're not, maybe not being honest with themselves.
I'm being authentic.
I'm not wearing makeup that trigger some girls because they aren't doing that.
And they're, I'm at it themselves.
You know what I mean?
So who does she think she heard a little bit?
Like, you know, I've had people upset at me for being nice.
I've had so many women not like me because of how genuinely nice I am.
It's because they don't feel free to do that because they have to have this guard up.
I don't have a guard up.
I'm very open.
You had definitely not.
I think that so many people are so unaware of their own guards, their own masks, their own armor, that they're,
that they're like pushing up against themselves.
Yeah.
Well, I realize, I don't think people, you know, like, sometimes people are doing something that bothers you.
I'm like, but they're not trying to bother you.
Like, you are just being bothered by it, but that's probably not their intention.
Like, someone cut you off.
That's going to keep happening until it doesn't bother you.
People coming off, I'm like, who even taught us that term?
Like, maybe they're busy.
Maybe they're bad just died.
Maybe they're going to a appointment.
Like, you do not know what people are going through.
I've got people off on accident.
Oh, okay.
You know what I mean?
Driving is a great way to test your triggers, right?
Oh, driving is a great way.
If you think that you're like, totally control of your emotions, but you still get road-rages, that's something where I'm like, oh, I'm cool,
come collected guy, like, whatever.
I can keep my shit to myself, then I would notice how to get road-rages, or somebody would be going 68 in the
Fastlane on the freeway.
And I'm like, I'm going to write the rest because so they know that I'm telling them.
I'm not, right?
Yeah.
I'm not going to ask.
It's the cool story that Pop the Man Head is you were talking about this.
I'm talking about like following intuition, right?
So, you know, think about, let's say words like manifest, words like,
I'll just tell the story.
So essentially, I was out loud.
I knew that I was working on my road-rage, and I was actually, so I was driving back home.
And I was in Lexington, coming back.
I was going to take the background here to Caspera.
And I was behind this old person who was going dangerously,
it's just 25 and a 45.
And I rode there, but just what I've been thinking about it.
And I started to get annoyed.
And I was like, you know what, I'm not in a rush right now.
I don't, I don't get, I'm not dying to get home.
What am I going to do with it?
I'm going to listen to the same podcast I'm listening to right now.
Like, so I, right?
So I hung a left.
I was like, let's just, let's go the long way.
Even if I'm behind him, I'm going to be a couple minutes behind him.
That's fine.
I won't even catch up.
So I went the long way, right?
And I'm going through and I didn't realize that I was driving past someone.
Essentially it was a distant family member on Shaley side of the family.
It was standing in her front yard.
I was like, I forgot to lift you.
I was standing in her front yard.
Looking at her front yard, she just moved the lawn.
And she's just going through a recent divorce.
She was literally just like, I hope I'm doing this right.
I talked to her for a few minutes.
He stopped.
And we have this conversation.
And I was driving away and she texted me this long thing.
Like, hey, thanks for, like, I needed that little conversation sort of thing.
And it was just this, so that's why I was trying to,
I was trying to connect the words like manifest words like, uh, intuition.
Like follow, follow the good and your part in your soul.
Like when you, like so, so me, I was trying to take care of myself,
not because I'm, I was trying to change my perspective of,
I don't want to be a real rich guy.
I don't want to be angry.
What?
This guy driving slow should not affect me.
That's my problem.
And I should figure it out.
So me following and wanting to heal that led to me healing someone else.
Helping someone a little bit.
And it's so important, right?
So and I think that a huge thing that
Life starts opened these doors.
The universe did that for you.
Absolutely.
That guy was put their fore...
What if he was in there, like it's, I was saying,
this is my head, like, but that happened for you.
A lot of people, why does it's happening to me?
I mean, that, that, too many words.
Change that to for me.
Love that.
Why is it's happening for me?
I've been in, like, a car accident.
I was the best day in my life.
I literally...
You almost died.
Yeah, it was the best day of my life.
I had an out of body experience.
It was the most spiritual day of my life.
I felt so blessed.
I should have flipped, but I didn't.
It was like, but you know what I mean?
You need to change your perspective on your life.
You can change those words.
You know, if you grew up in a negative home, it's harder, but you can change it.
Especially if you're with negative people, your partners negative or like your friends
are native.
And unfortunately, sometimes, if they're not willing to change, like, I had used this term.
You got to rise up for yourself.
Like it.
It's really hard.
It is, but you have to do it for you.
Yeah.
Because no one's going to do it for you, but you.
It's so important to like take that stand and be like, you know, like, you don't have
to stay with the same friends.
If they're not, if they're not matching up, if they're...
No, maybe if they're being your friends.
Yeah.
But when you're, when I'm seeing my friends do things that I don't want to do or only talk
about other people, you know, the small town gossip, but then, and then, and then,
and then.
That just doesn't light me up.
And I'm all about lighting my soul up.
Like light me up spiritually, so fully.
I don't need to have these kind of conversation as my daily with my partner.
Like, I need this.
Um, I hate the small talk.
It's like cringe to me.
How are you?
Good.
Like, like, by.
And they both, both parties know that like, we don't really want to be saying this.
We're not care.
And I don't care.
And the truth is, sometimes I don't care how you're doing, because sometimes I just,
I'm not that mindset where, I don't care.
It's not a bad thing to not care all the people.
You don't know them.
Why do you care?
You can't be walking, if you walk around the town
and you see 1700 people, you can't take the stress
of I need to know how every single 1700 of these people are.
100%.
It's not my job.
Yeah.
Because what happens to me is if I engage people read it wrong,
people think I'm hitting on them or people like,
all right.
And it's like, just because I'm asking them
if you like your job, it doesn't mean that I'm like hitting on you.
People will take nice, like my boyfriend always says,
like, people take your nicest for granted.
And it's, but I'm not going to stop being me.
But I've had these conversations
that my coffee shop or people write down in tears
because they're telling me things they've never talked about.
So sometimes you do have that ability
no matter where you're working.
When you, if you get that urge and the girlfriend
who's started to hey, go talk to someone, go do it.
Definitely.
I love that.
Do you know what I mean?
Do you ever get that?
And you see someone and you're like, I want to go talk to them.
Oh, no, that's weird.
Right.
I'm going to talk to them.
That person is so thankful.
Well, in being open to who they are,
like, giving them a little bit of room to,
you know, you love to be heard.
Yeah, definitely.
And I think that a time going back to where you're talking about,
like a lot of older people feel a little disconnected.
I think in ways a lot of, you know,
just listening to someone who needs someone to talk to.
Right now, I always think about,
think about nowadays, you're cooking some something.
Like, like, you and your partner are cooking something
back in the day you would text your mom or call your mom
or ask your mom, okay, what's the ingredient for this
and grandma taught her?
And whatever, but nowadays, you mom doesn't exist in that.
You just look to Google.
Google has the answer for that recipe or how long you cook it.
I just think of all these technology has changed a lot of different
areas of our life, not just like cooking and getting recipes,
where we've cut out a lot of our,
that's the older people and just other people.
So I feel like we're connected through the internet,
but we are very disconnected.
And sometimes we're reminded in situations like this,
where you're like, follow your intuition, talk to that person
if you think you need to.
And I feel like some people do not know how to communicate.
I actually think a lot of the population
cannot have a genuine conversation
because they, they aren't authentic with themselves,
so how can they be authentic with me?
And I see that a lot.
I can tell so much by someone by what they talk about to me
in the first two seconds.
So there's this technique where you ask them
how they're doing and they talk any way one, two, three,
before you respond.
And then they'll talk again in you wait one, two,
before you respond because people wait silence, right?
Oh, right.
So if you don't talk, they'll feel the void
and it's always interesting to see what people have to say
because you can learn so much from someone
by just listening.
I usually like to be, I used to grow up like talk,
like talk, talk, talk, talk, talk,
because I've ADHD, whatever.
But like my recent years, I like to listen
because I'm learning more when I'm listening.
You know what I mean?
And also I'm like coming into these crazy conversations
with these crazy random people,
but it's like, wow, my life manifests
at some amazing conversations with crazy people.
And we each have something to teach,
which is like this podcast.
That's what it is.
It's a matter of who it is.
Like, some of the gas station,
like don't be like, oh, they haven't been teaching me.
Everyone has something to teach you
because you all had different life experiences.
And I also believe we're all messengers.
Nothing's random.
Sometimes you hear a random statement
and you take it for granted.
But everything you are hearing in your life,
you are meant to hear.
Even if it's on the radio,
even if it's on the outlist,
and the commercial, they're ads
because it's like subliminal messaging.
But if you hear something on the radio,
like, and it resonates with you
and it triggers this emotion or something like,
the universe is a frequency and you're tuning in.
So like everything you're hearing
is you're supposed to hear.
Yeah, but I feel like so many people,
because I always wonder, like, okay,
what's the difference?
Like let's say now versus before, for me,
just using me as an example again.
Like, like if there was these messages,
these like, man, follow this,
like, here's what you need to go through right now.
Like a lot of times it's hard to,
like, you don't feel like that till later.
Right, yeah, but do you think just by being,
like, honestly, it seems like just by being open.
And like, so if someone approaches you,
you're in a bad mood, someone approaches you,
instead of being like, I'm in a bad mood.
I don't, like, let's get this conversation over with
because I don't want to talk to this person
because I'm feeling this.
Well, they can feel that.
Yeah, but if you, but what about if you instead
stay open to this person?
Well, think about this story you told me about earlier, right?
Oh, oh, oh, on Halloween.
Halloween, yeah.
We can talk about that.
Yeah, it's up to your personal stuff.
Certainly, so, so, so I'll retell it.
So something that I felt the need to tell Jay
when she got here two years ago.
And I think I've mentioned this night
on the podcast somewhere at some point.
Oh, wow.
Maybe episode 14.
I don't think that I mentioned you in it,
but I essentially two nights before a big Halloween show,
we were renting out this place.
And I was throwing a big event.
And I did the decor and DJ at all night.
And the graphics.
And I like trying to take care of all of it,
like the events side of things.
I like doing the whole big thing.
But two days before this, my hard drive crashed,
which means that I had to scramble to get all my music
and try to find it.
And I'm like waiting on different loading screens.
And I don't know where half my songs are.
And some of them got to late.
It's all this.
It was two days of not a lot of sleep, if any,
and a lot of stress.
And then I had to leave for an away show the next morning.
Essentially, I was very stressed.
It's going through it in Jay came up
and because we've been like friends in different ways.
Like we're always happy to see each other.
We've been friends in different ways.
We're not super close.
Well, she came up and...
I'm gonna go.
While you're DJing.
Yeah.
Like, while I was up there.
Which is not me.
I usually don't do that.
I mean, I like to be at the stage,
but not like that.
Right.
No, but what I, the reason why I felt compelled to tell you
was because it was kind of weird, but it was...
Or I'll leave finish.
What was I doing?
So you came up and you, not like right away.
Like you just came up and started rubbing my back.
But you came up and you were saying nice things to me.
You're like, you're doing great.
Like you were essentially, you were encouraging me.
But I was inside what was happening was I was very stressed.
I was having a five, six hour long panic attack
and to want things down.
Probably negative and maybe you're mind.
I was very negative.
I was very...
My suicidal thoughts were just...
Like that night was very a suicidal contemplation night.
And so heavy.
Yeah.
But what I told you when you got here that story is,
is I remember you coming up and trying to help me.
And I was so focused on my own thing.
I didn't realize what was going on.
It was like this, like...
I know who you are, but you're bugging me sort of thing.
And I remember, I snapped at you.
I was like, you need to get off stage,
like, please leave me alone.
And I remember the reason why I remember it
is because that moment, you're reaction to it.
Made me realize what I said.
Made me realize what I was doing.
Like, I don't want to snap at people.
Like, I'm being aggressive.
I'm being mean.
I don't...
What am I doing?
Yeah.
So, because you were instantly...
Like, okay, I get it.
I understand.
I'm probably done.
So, like you walked away, like sad.
And it just stuck with me because I was like,
that's how, like, I was feeling this thing
and meeting one sentence was enough
to just shove it right into the end.
But it's like how I reacted is how you are reflection
of how you're feeling inside.
Because I'm an empath.
So, I'm trying to give you all this love
because I'm empath to empath.
And I could feel...
I was very drunk that night.
But I could feel even in your music,
that something was different.
I could tell you were stressed.
I could feel, I mean, you always play good music,
but it was something it wasn't you.
That was way off.
Yeah. Like, it wasn't as heartful
and like everything kind of wasn't working,
but it was an inner reflection of you.
It wasn't working because you were working inside.
Right.
How I interpreted it.
Yeah, absolutely.
And like me rubbing your back, yeah, it's not.
Like out of context for like...
But it was like, it was like black.
That was that point.
So, it's crazy that I'm doing this,
like, as a healer and more like open to like touching you.
Because I was like drunk, but it was like,
I could sense it so much.
And you really needed that, obviously,
because it's stuck with you.
And that's why I want to say that
what you do for people, you might think it's minor,
but it plays an impact, the butterfly effect.
Showing compassion when they're not showing compassion
towards themselves is everything.
Seriously.
You don't know what you're doing.
Like the moment where you made me snap out of my stuff,
I mean, I made me snap out of my stuff,
my meat meat of a foreign person.
My kindness, my friend, yeah.
It's trick of you because you were not that way
and you want to be that way.
And that's who you are in the heart.
And snapped in this person County that wasn't really you,
but it was you at that time.
And you, by me, seeing sad,
you were able to see like an internal reflection of you
on someone else because of her mirrors, right?
Exactly.
And you're like, whoa, I don't want to be like that.
Or wow, why was I like that?
And the world comes rushing in and you're like,
what, you know, you look at you,
stop these crazy thoughts that have been catapulting you
for hours and days, whatever.
And you almost become present with what's going on.
Well, like when I was coming here, like,
me being like a light worker, like worker
is just basically someone who's mission is to come race
a frequency of the planet.
I have known that for a while.
I like walked into a room in this one of my psychic teachers,
like, oh, you're a light worker.
Like, she can see it.
So people can see it in your aura.
That's like, you know, when you walk into a room,
people always look at you.
Because people can feel your energy.
I've always felt like I'm very comfortable to be around.
I feel like I'm very, people can be open with me.
I've never had people open up too easily.
It means sometimes.
But that's why I'm here on the planet.
And once you step into that role,
you just like, nothing, it surprises me anymore.
Like, nothing.
Like picking up a piece of trash, you know,
instead of being angry at that trash,
be thankful that trash is there to pick up
because you pick it up and you might inspire someone else
to do the same?
Exactly. Exactly.
I talk about Travis Pastrana, motor cross guy.
Back in the day, I remember when I was young,
he did the first back flip.
And it was like, what?
Oh, my God.
I mean, my buddies were just freaking out.
But then like weeks later, like, just weeks.
Nobody had ever done this weeks later.
Multiple people are doing back flips.
Catalysts.
It's, it's, it's, you know.
Yes, you can't see it.
Sometimes you have to see it in someone else.
But I talk to you, know about being empath and being.
Everyone is psychic, that's listening.
Everyone has powers.
You just don't realize that.
They're powers because it's you.
But you ever like know something intuitively?
That's psychic.
Like, don't think of psychic as a little crazy little ball.
And I got to go pay to see the future.
Right. Right. Right. Right.
Everyone has these gifts.
And everyone has a reason that they're here on the planet.
Nothing is random.
Like, I always talk about, this is the greatest,
biggest shift that the galaxy has ever seen.
And you are here on it.
Like, it's here for a reason.
If you're listening to this, you're listening to this for a reason.
Right.
Do you know what I mean?
And like, it's nothing is random.
I always talk about that.
Like, it's not random.
If your life sucks, change your perception.
I don't know what I mean.
I know it's hard.
And it's like, because I've been low.
Like, I've been there before where I didn't get out of bed.
And that's dark.
I'm depressed.
And I don't know what I want to do with my life.
And little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit.
Not good enough.
And little bit of a, but like, take that time to just rest.
And it's okay to be like that.
And that's the thing.
If you are depressed right now,
it's okay because it can get better.
Right.
So you have anxiety.
Like, it's okay.
Like, it's going to be okay.
And that's the thing, because people have been through
worse and they're okay.
Like, you can do it.
It doesn't matter where you're at.
Like, it's going to be okay.
Yeah.
If you follow the thought, instead of just doing your best to avoid the thought,
and distract yourself from the thought,
I know it's, you don't always want to get into the ring with a thought,
and think that you can just stranglet when you're feeling anxiety,
you're very depressed, of course.
But when you feel that you can, like,
all right, why am I feeling like that?
Like, let's see if I can work this out.
I'm in an emotionally balanced state.
Yeah.
You know, what times have you follow the thought of fear?
It's, it just, it leads all the way back to like,
a simple fear.
Like, I'm a fear.
I'm afraid of, so say like you having anxiety
and your heart's just going like,
you know, am I going to die?
Am I going to die?
And if you just follow these thoughts back,
you know, from a sane position, it's like,
I'm not going to die.
I'm kind of talking about that.
Yeah.
We were talking about something with an edible too.
Yeah, I took some streams and I took an edible.
And my heart was like,
oh, right, right, right, right, right.
I could feel it like in my toes.
And I was like, oh my god, my anxiety, like,
like I'm going to die a little bit,
but I knew that somehow I'm going to go out
and not going to pat die on my bed and my tiny house at 24
from streams and an edible.
Like, and once I just accepted it,
I stopped feeling my heart, I just felt
oneness and connection and I just was.
And I can't.
When you tap into the frequency of the universe
and you just are, it's just like,
it's almost like you're breathing for the first time,
like, that's how it felt.
Like, just, you just feel like it just is.
Like, it just is.
It just is.
Like, it's just, it's like, ego dissolved.
You dissolve.
I'm not male.
I'm not female.
I'm not a nurse.
Like, I'm not this.
I'm not bad.
I don't live in Kelsau.
None of that matters, right?
It just, do you see the, I see like,
so many like, like, suicide in MDMA and like the research
that are doing, of course around my killing depression
and it requires your brain.
Oh yeah, it's a special thing.
The numbers, listen to if you haven't heard much about this,
the numbers are through the roof like,
people like PTSD, like, if there's so many great,
yeah, microdosing and suicide.
There's a lot of states and stuff that are very quickly
making things, organs getting on it.
Like, decriminalizing and I'm excited for the future.
What a, I love to talk about this too.
The government makes it so illegal
because it doesn't want its people to wake the fuck up
and see how corrupt the world is.
Because when you take shrooms, you see it for how it is,
there's no veil.
And you also begin to love yourself
and the government doesn't want you to love yourself
because guess what, we are powerful.
Yeah. They can't buy us when we're like powerful beings
and we realize we are the creators of our life.
They can't control you anymore.
Yep.
When you're brainwashed in your sheep,
which is fine if you're there,
but you have the power to wake up.
And this is like what the podcast is,
it's the way right now.
Everyone's waking up faster numbers
than everyone 2020 hit.
They and we, we're building people are waking up so fast
and like what the fuck is this energy inside of me?
Right, right, right, right.
Why am I just quitting my job?
Like, I don't want to do this.
Like, blah, blah, blah and people are like,
waking up like,
I mean, that's what I have.
I have multiple people on the podcast,
Entrepreneur's Business owners who are more recently
like I do realize that I wasn't happy
and so I had to do what made me happy.
And here's what I'm doing and it's great.
Literally. That's in your universe.
I wish you.
Yeah.
It supports you because
everyone here has a unique frequency to their soul
and you have a unique gifts that you came here to do.
And if you're not tapping into that,
you're gonna feel dead for me.
Most of it.
And almost anyone, if you don't feel like you were belong here
or you don't feel like you have a purpose,
you're not gonna feel alive.
Right.
You're gonna feel in that rack.
And that's super hard because it's hard to figure out
what you want to do, but you start with what makes you happy.
Exactly. Oh, that's what I was totally just gonna say.
So like a music, my thing with music,
I, you know, through, let's say,
okay, let's start for me, trauma and trying to just get away
from the world around me.
I was a walk man, Discman guy.
Like, just give me music.
I'm putting headphones on so I can escape what's going around.
I had a lot of time by myself.
A lot of time, like walking places by myself.
So following that, so as I get older.
I got, I never picked up, I mean, I picked up a guitar,
like kind of dingled around on it just myself,
but I never, and never in choir, never in music classes, orchestra,
any of these things, but I just kept as life goes on following it.
I'm like, oh, okay, I get older and I,
I didn't know exactly what I wanted to do,
but the way I was able to quit my meal job was finally,
I was like, okay, I got to take this leap and do school.
I was like, I don't know what I want to do still.
I don't know the answers, but I do love music.
Yeah.
And it feels like that.
And so I started going after it, and then it teaches me all this audio stuff.
And now I'm an audio engineer, now I have this podcast.
And just, so essentially, one thing after another,
just following this, my love and allowing myself to say,
like, you know what, you do love music, and that's so, okay,
and there can be something there.
Like, maybe you haven't discovered it yet, but you can search for it.
And I think just, you know, when you make that step of quitting,
it's scary.
Oh, no doubt.
Like, like, it's like the stability, right?
But the universe grants you the sevenfold, like,
one thing, you leave one bad thing behind, not bad,
but like something you, it's making you miserable.
Doesn't match up with you.
And when you cut that off, you're DNA, like,
did it like, like, rewires, and then you start doing
with what you align with, and then it's going to go bam, bam, bam, bam,
and you're going to meet people who support you and like, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
well, the the the the the the the the the the the it's it's so crazy.
Oh, go on up.
Uh, the chair just keeps letting down, but it's it's crazy.
Like, at first, I feel like I didn't give it to myself, like, I would do this
school, and then I just felt like such a fool.
And I, I feel like, but that's ego.
Right.
I know that there was this, like, falling period.
I'm not going to make enough.
No one's going to listen.
I'm not good enough.
Yeah, I'm not going to do it.
Yeah, I need to like support me.
Exactly.
Like, yeah, I just just thought in your head.
That's not soul.
That's how you know, soul is love fear is ego.
So if you're getting negative thoughts, you can go, okay,
and you don't have to dismiss your ego, but you can say, okay,
you go, I hear you, but where is my soul?
And then soul starts pouring in love.
Most definitely.
And you can do love after I do affirmations every day.
Yeah.
I am enough.
Say that and let yourself know.
I am an herbalist, like, I own a wellness center.
And you're demanding it.
We did, for, for New Year's a couple friends, a couple of our friends in
chain, we went to a new court.
We did vision books.
Yeah.
And I love, you know, and honestly, I'm not kidding.
I have it as we're walking downstairs.
We live our bedroom upstairs and it's on the wall.
I plan on moving in every few weeks because I don't want to get
get complacent about it.
Yeah.
But I honestly stop in the mornings in an off-genut night before I'm going to bed.
And I look at it.
And I'm like, I know these things are, is what I'm doing.
Yeah.
I don't know the timeline yet.
But like these are what this is what's happening.
This is who I am.
This is what's in, and I think we talk, my other friends
and I were talking more recently a lot about, like, a, like,
so church, for example, church a Sunday, like a service.
We were talking about the importance of maybe trying to have like an every other,
every other week or twice a month or something,
having like a Sunday get together with our friends and reconnecting with
these things.
Like, so kind of how we have our meditations that we every morning.
Like, I am a good person.
I'm, I'm a this.
I'm an herbalist.
I'm that, you know, you reaffirm.
If you have like a weekly or bi-weekly thing, even with your friends, where you out,
wow, like, community is everything that's happening.
Yeah.
So I like mentioning that on this podcast because if any listeners have like,
oh, I could do that with my friends, like, please do it.
Yeah.
Whatever pops into your brain right here, if anything, like, if you're like,
I have a couple of friends who'd probably get together, like,
try some months.
Let's just set six months aside and put it in the calendar right now.
You know.
And I, um, it's funny to say that because I am hosting my first full moon circle.
You are what?
Tell me about this.
Um, so Holly, my friend Holly, she's like a astrologer.
She's amazing.
Um, we've like wanted to do events forever and she just moved into this apartment.
And it has like a space.
So we rented the space and we're just hosting like a full moon event.
And we're gonna be talking like the moon and how to fix you.
And because like a lot of people don't know that the moon affects you.
Like, right.
Yeah.
We just use eyes and we're like that's not coming back.
Like a new new.
Yeah.
There's only a little bit of water in our body.
But we're 70 first-hand water.
The moon and the sky controls the tides, like, affects your inner tides.
Okay.
Right.
So the moon is in Leo.
And it's all about the sacred, solar, shock rugs, power.
I am enough.
And so we're just gonna, it's like, just a place for people to open up and just to connect
to a loud time to just connect.
I feel like so many people don't just allow time to like connect in a sober place.
Because like quit drinking.
That's what I told you.
So much of my get together.
So let's go grab a beer.
Which is fine.
Cool.
Fun.
But I want to like tell me your dreams and visions and let's talk about it.
And how can you get there?
Yeah.
Sometimes a bar it just doesn't open up that part of a conversation.
The energy is important.
I mean, it's Portland bars.
You know, I like to go to Portland bar.
It's so crafting and creative.
But I'm seeing like my friends just want to hang out.
Like I feel like we just have to like we need to like create.
Like I think I need to create a show and entertain all the time and like,
but it's like my friend just want to hang out.
Like get coffee and hang out.
Like it doesn't have to be like, let's go with fucked up and rage.
And because like that's such a big part of my identity.
And like a lot of people that know me, like I was always raging.
Like, since I was little like I've always been like,
party fun dancing.
Like, but you know,
when you just your friend just want to sit with you and be with you and just talk.
Yeah.
A lot of times like hang it out before you go to the bar at your house.
You're supposed to get together.
Yeah, that's like the best part.
Yeah.
It's like we need more of that.
That's super cool that you know what to call the moon thing one more time with it.
It's just full moon gathering.
Okay.
It's just like a place to come and learn and Holly's like again,
really in astrology.
So she's going to talk about how this the astrology of this full moon and how it affects you.
And personally, and in general, and then we're just going to kind of talk about how the
full moon affects you in general.
And then we'll do like a little ritual and each everyone's going to get like a crystal,
which is related to the full moon and how to use crystals if you don't know anything about them.
You get to take it home and then I'll be doing like affirmations that you can take home
and just just a place for like people to come and connect.
Right.
You know what I mean?
It's so cool.
And it's, you know, like the way that I see the talk about my timeline.
Like, oh, take a look at that.
It's cool to see like, you know, in five years, whatever the equivalent of this little event
you're doing, like, what can that be?
Like, maybe it's going to be this music.
You're going to put a people, maybe there's, you know, who knows?
Holly says, well, like, it's, I know this is like ego or not, but I have dreams where I'm talking
in front of a lot of people.
Mm.
I think.
With their hands up, like not like it's like religious, but it's like, I feel like I met, I feel like I have this voice
in this wisdom, this internal book and like what's the point of keeping it in.
Right.
I feel like it's a disservice to the universe to not share like my knowledge.
I'm beginning to feel that way more and more.
I'm like, I have to.
Like, I'm supposed to be able to be right this thing.
Like, yeah, and maybe we don't get it, but what I'm realizing is people are coming out to me
and saying, remember when you said this to me, well, like, did it?
I'm like, I don't remember saying that at all.
Oh, my gosh, totally totally.
But I'm yes because you are planting the seeds, right?
You know, you, your people might not understand you when you're saying,
you might not vibe with this podcast, but you're hearing it.
You're subconscious is hearing it and you're subconscious vibes with it.
Yep.
Your ego might not vibe with it, but something is hearing it and it's, your subconscious doesn't forget.
Right.
That's what I notice a lot of my mother living with me.
A lot of this stuff, I hit a lot of instant, like I'll say something or she'll be, for example,
she'll be walking in the kitchen, I was listening to something while I'm cooking.
And she'll say something and she'll say something uncomfortable or a joke about it or make fun of it or whatever.
And I let it go because in a couple days, she'll go back.
Yeah, and she'll almost be listening to the same thing, but she'll find a way to maybe bring it up.
Yeah, bring it up.
You did kind of think about it.
But at first, you got to realize you're so right.
At first, there is part of us, we're like, why, I don't know what this is.
And if you just stay up, stay open to it and a lot of times it's working in the back of your mind for you.
Well, if you would've told me like four years ago that I wouldn't be drinking,
right.
Yeah, right.
Like that's such a big part of me, but I just kind of like,
with not drinking, I just realize that it's not going to get me personally to where I want to go.
And I'm not one of those people that can just have one.
Right.
And I know that about myself, so why even go there?
My partners recover.
My mom, my dad, like, I'm breaking the trauma.
Like, my mom has nine years clean next month, and it's like, I want to be like that.
Wonderful.
Like, I want to be like that.
Like, I don't want a substance to control me.
Because alcohol does.
Like, when I, when I start, I want more.
Yeah.
And I want it the next day.
And the next, even if I'm hung over, like, I'm like, oh, one can I go better to drink again.
And it's like this parasite inside my brain.
And it's like craving alcohol.
It's like what really wants it, though.
What don't I want to feel?
And same with smoking, I'm like, I've been a stoner for like 10 years, but lately I quit smoking.
Because I'm, I was numbing it out.
Yeah.
Mary and Wana.
I mean, it's good for my anxiety.
Yeah, it's legal.
Yeah, it helps me sleep.
But it was, it was, it was numbing me out.
It was like, yeah, it's, it does numbing me out.
Definitely does.
Right.
I mean, I, I still smoke quite a bit too.
I'm trying to figure out like what this phase of my face.
Why do we look, why?
What am I missing?
And then I just started to really,
and that's why I kind of could coffee because I'm like,
I've never been cleaned from any substance.
I've always had a stimulant or we, I love to drink coffee and then smoke a bowl.
Right.
I mean, I do too, but the, that's the thing is we don't really stop and say like,
oh, like, what am I without these things?
Like, like, and that's where I'm at.
Yeah.
And it's so hard.
So how do you feel?
Like you've been, you've been not drinking and you decide
that you're like, we're talking about earlier.
Like, I don't want to.
It's crazy because as soon as I said, I didn't want to.
And I like put it on Instagram.
I wanted to.
It's like the devil's advocate, right?
It's like, but I realize that I don't, like, I don't want to.
Like, what am I getting out of it?
What, how much money have I spent?
How many nights don't I remember?
How many things have I done that I wouldn't have done sober?
I mean, how many times have I, like, I'm like, how am I alive sometimes?
Like, the situations I get myself into?
And I just realize I'm like, I'm not leading by an example.
I don't want someone to, that's not who I want people to be like.
I don't encourage people to be like that.
I want people to be encouraged by positivity and self-love.
And stepping onto your comfort zone and just being you.
And when I was drinking or smoking, it wasn't, it wasn't me,
but it wasn't like the person that I wanted to be.
Right. And you knew that and you feel that next day you wake up and you feel like
I was getting sick after one beer, I was hung over.
Right.
I used to drink like a fifth and shot like beer and wine and that mixed everything.
And like, but I was getting sick after one beer.
Yeah, it's like it's constant signals of like, okay, like this isn't
benefiting you any more. My soul and my temple was no more.
No more. And like, I smell bad, you know, you stink and like you care in your skin.
Your pores just leak different smells when you're drinking.
I just didn't want to be that anymore. I'm not saying I will ever drink again,
because I mean, like, I can't control the future, but it is my intention to not drink.
Love it. That's great.
Yeah, I'm glad I, I think a lot of people are age.
It's such a societal norm to drink. Like me, I've been drinking since I was, I think, 14.
Same.
Yeah, in the back of the car.
With all the caffeine, yeah.
Yeah, little did you know, listener, a forelocal used to kill you.
Yeah.
That thing to, they still do, I think.
But it is weird though, you know, we don't, it's not like,
oh, everybody who drinks is bad.
No, that's exactly what I was going to say.
It's, it's, sometimes you like, we get thrown into our life, like, this light, like,
we're doing this thing that everybody's been telling us to do.
We're following, it's not like we're like being crappy people.
We're working during the week.
We're doing what everybody needs to do.
And it's like, you go and enjoy yourself on the weekend.
But sometimes you got to be like, okay, when I'm on my deathbed, when I'm like,
okay, I lived my life to the fullest, because everybody wants that.
Everybody wants to say, like, I've done,
done the things I wanted to work with.
I've had the best days ever drinking.
It's not that I disagree with it.
Right.
It's fun.
But a lot of times we don't, I feel like we lack the, like,
do I want to do this right now?
Like we, we lack being able to stop ourselves and be like,
I am kind of planning just for the next weekend, aren't I?
Or, or whatever it may be.
I think, well, that's another thing too, is like, we look so much forward to the weekends
to get fucked up to not remember.
Why are we looking forward to not remembering?
Because we don't want to feel and we want to check the fuck out.
Why are we looking forward to not remembering our lives?
Because we're not happy.
I always say, I like saying, like, when you're, when it's late at night,
and you've had to be drinking and you're like deciding to drink more,
or for me, like when it would be okay, when I'd be like,
oh, I'm going to do cocaine tonight.
I would always tell myself, well, you're going to do that,
but you're making the choice to borrow some happiness from tomorrow.
Really?
Like, a lot of it, a lot of the times, a lot of our weekend drinking when it comes to, like,
oh, it's been literally every weekend this year, I drink.
Sometimes it's like, what, what am I borrowing happiness from?
Am I borrowing happiness?
Like, weekend by weekend from next year in my life?
You know, I'm not to mention, of course, you know, for me, personally,
I cannot drink without having a burrito afterwards.
I feel like I'm just going to eat bad.
Oh, man, it just comes with food.
And the next day, I eat bad and like,
yeah, because you're hung over and justify why you should eat bad and hung over.
Yeah.
I think taking a look at these things is super important, and you make the decision.
But it's just really like, is that what you want?
Or is it just so habitual to work the Monday through Friday and then go out Friday,
Saturday because you don't like your week.
Right. Right.
You know what I mean?
Instead, why don't you look like I can't wait to come home meditate and just sit with
myself and like read.
You know what I mean?
Find different thing.
And I think a lot of it, too, is people don't know what to do when they have
free time.
They can't just be with themselves with their partner and just sit.
I have so many friends that their partners and they can't like be sober together
and they're like, they think they have to get drunk.
You know, a lot of relationships start from the bar and start from getting drunk together.
And that's how we've always been and that's how it is.
I don't want to be around them so work because I don't like them or I don't like myself.
Well, yeah, that's tough.
That's like a lot of partners they just drink and that's what they do.
Well, with mine, my partner doesn't drink.
So I was drinking by myself.
Like this is dumb.
Yeah, you're like, wait, do I like this?
But if he was still drinking, I can't say I would be done.
Do you know what I mean?
He was almost like that catalyst where it's like, why am I drinking by myself?
Yeah, it's like him doing that kind of made you take a look at like,
do I want to do this?
Yeah, I want to not do this.
Yeah, because he's over it.
Like he spent all this life, you know, using substances to numb it out.
And here I am still like drinking by myself at restaurants and he's not.
And like, I just realized too, like I was drinking so much because I wasn't in control.
And I could blame the alcohol for my actions.
Right.
I was really mean when I'm drunk.
Right. Yeah, like losing, losing the control.
I think a lot of people, you talk to a lot of people when it comes to alcohol and you get down to it.
A lot of times they'll say the sentence, why I'm just a control person.
I feel like I can get that off to them.
I'm a control person because I say the same thing too, right?
Yeah.
I think a lot of alcohol sometimes for me, it seemed like it would shut my mind down.
Like I would use, when I was working on where house or how to come home and I'm like,
I'm just so like, I can't sleep in the am so like whatever.
And so.
So present.
Yeah, and so you drink.
And yeah.
But it's a touchy subject because there are a lot of listeners still drinking.
Nothing is wrong with that.
I'm just on a different path than a lot of people.
And I'm aware of that.
No doubt.
But the people that I look up to, they don't drink.
That's also one of my Buddha.
Gandhi.
Well, the Teresa, like the people that are my
Muses, they don't, they didn't drink.
And it's like, I'm trying to walk in these, not saying that I'm Buddha or Gandhi,
more the Teresa because I'm not by any means.
Those are people that I look up to.
If that's a reference, anybody just drew that there in saying.
Like I'm not saying I'm these people, but these are the people that I look up to.
These are the people that I see when I'm meditating.
Yeah.
So it's like, I want to embody that energy and these people weren't.
There you are doing those kind of things.
And I want to be more like the people I look up to, right?
And they weren't drinking.
And I think that so many people, again, it's a touchy subject because like,
you think that you're being attacked.
You feel like, well, why I have my reason for Boba and we all do.
And that's so okay.
Like I am so, you know, everybody has their vices.
Yeah.
I've had mine.
I have mine.
I think like, you know, we all have to experience them in different things.
But I think the biggest thing is just having that moment, like I was saying when I was driving
in the car and I'm like, oh, I'm going to take a left here.
And I'm going to, like, I don't want to feel this anger, this road rage.
Yeah.
So like when it comes time, like sometimes just breaking your habits of like,
you're planning on going to the bar and Friday or Saturday and like just this weekend don't go.
And then maybe say like, what do I actually want to do?
Like what?
And if you think about it, it's like, you know what?
I love snowboarding.
I'm going to go snowboarding.
I love, oh, there's a conference for this computer program that I like
in Portland.
I'm going to go try that out.
Like just follow your interests and follow.
Yeah.
What you're trying to.
Like so what I spend a lot of my free time is going to nurseries or going to pet stores
or going to new parks or going to new places outside.
Or going into like, bothiques.
Like, because I like to see people's craft.
Oh, heck you know what I mean?
I like Portland is like my place.
Like I love going into new stores and I love going into plant.
I love plants.
But it also inspires me.
So doing these things is inspiring me and reminding me what I love.
It's like when I walk into a plant store, I'm like, like I just went to pollen yesterday.
Oh yeah.
Or storm like, oh my gosh, I love it.
And so it's totally cute.
And they they deck out like the outside.
They've painted the outside.
The interior is always like my face off of this all day.
It's great.
But when you like something you follow that and inspires you.
So do things that inspire you.
Yeah.
Like if you want to open a bar then yeah, and keep going to bars like if that's like your dream you love beer
and you want to bury go for it.
But like if you want to do something and that's something I also want to encourage people,
you can do whatever you want to do.
And doesn't matter.
Oh, I've been working this job for 10 years.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Whatever you want to do, you can stop and start and do it.
It really sucks in the beginning because you're like maybe not getting as much like I'm living
paycheck to paycheck.
What I know that financial abundance is coming.
Like it will happen to me.
You're not terrified.
I'm not having a physical time.
No, because you know what I was working as a nurse and I hated my life.
I was not happy.
I wasn't who I was.
Not saying that like I just need to better protect myself.
Like I'm applying to the hospital.
But it's like I know it's short term.
Right.
But I feel like what was happening is like I when I go into this job,
like I was going to be there for six months.
I was there for 10.
So it's like I'm just like and I started to hate like the people I was helping.
And I was like resizing it and like if you start to feel like that,
I was like I need to quit because this isn't good for the people
and so many nurses are burnt out and they can't recognize that and take the
break for themselves.
Yeah and they need to.
I mean nurses are definitely that's something like I feel like to be honest with
Shaley.
I feel like more and more I'm always like trying to push her to like make sure you
take care of yourself.
But we don't, right?
And yeah, you know, but it's something that she's more and more and more
aware of it and making sure she doesn't just like hold everybody's stuff all day
and she puts it down and she gets home and it's important.
But I think a lot of us need to or could a lot of us could benefit from seeing that,
like you know, maybe don't want to do that this time and I want to follow this other
intuition.
Yeah and I just like to say like what did you want to do in your kid?
Because really what did you want to do with your kid?
Like you know, I want to do this.
What you can do that.
Like my boyfriend like my gosh.
You know, like the squirrel suits?
That's literally what he wants to do.
So like, oh my, I don't know how that's a career, but let's go for it.
Like let's start jumping out of play.
Like he literally like since he's little like he just wants to like jump out of
shit, like adrenaline, right?
Like that's what gets him alive.
Like this mundane like he needs adrenaline.
Right.
Hard to get drug addict and using heroin and everything.
You need that adrenaline, right?
Like heart pounding.
So like he wants to do that.
I'm like, I don't know how that's a career, but let's go for it.
Yeah, follow it.
Yeah and like you just start by jumping out planes and you just
keep going and like maybe you can instruct people how to jump out of planes.
I don't know, but who might have told you that your dream is dumb?
That's another thing.
People like you can't do that.
Right.
Why not?
Sometimes I think that that when it comes like dreams, like we see a lot of, we mix up a lot of
like talent with dreams.
A lot of like, oh well, this person, I saw a video of this person when they were six and they were singing.
So they've been born with that talent.
But if you don't have to have like something that you were born with,
no.
What did you love?
What did you enjoy?
What were you drawn to?
How now it's like it's not like how do I make this full-time career right this second?
It's like, no, no.
It takes time.
Yeah, point yourself out and start walking.
You just start doing like another thing I talk about.
Oprah always says, so full Sunday's the most important thing you can give yourself as time.
And I know you have time to meditate two minutes a day.
I always tell people you don't have time.
How much are you on your phone?
What's your screen time?
Yeah.
Every time you check.
How, you know what I mean?
Like you have the time you're just not choosing to use the time for what you want.
Because a lot of it is again lack of self-love, not feeling,
I don't deserve this time.
I don't deserve to do what I want to do because I'm not good enough.
Or my parents, you know, that's how I move.
And it's like this cycle and it's like, it's really time to break free and just step into your power.
Yes.
Truly.
I feel like, I don't know.
I feel like I just, it feels right.
That's what I'm doing.
It feels in it feels right.
But I feel like you are doing that.
Like embodying it and you're going for it and who said you would 3,000 people listening already,
and you just started it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just started it.
And it's this like, you know, I was serious about it of course, but the podcast,
it wasn't like, I'm going to do a podcast and that's my destiny, this sort of thing.
But it definitely feels very like, like, whatever comes after this or whatever this leads to,
or even if I do a 1,000 episode, like it does feel very right, it feels very correct.
When I'm like editing the video for that show.
I do.
Yeah, I, I, I, I'm reminded, I'm like, oh, okay, like,
and honestly, it helps me fill my own self-love.
Like a lot of people, you know, sometimes it's so profound.
I'm like, it even tears me up sometimes when I'm recording podcasts,
but they're telling me something very emotional,
if they're like, they open up to me.
Not only to me, but on my podcasts and on, like, they trust me to take what they have to say.
And I'm going to hold it and, and present it in whatever way, you know.
So it's, things just start feeling right.
And I think believing that that is possible.
It's definitely a self-love technique.
It's a knowing that you'll heal over time and waiting and being patient.
I always like to talk about, like, Oprah was fired from her job, fired from her job, like Oprah, right?
And she said it was the best thing that ever happened to her,
because she was not supposed to be there.
A lot of people we look up to their lives just didn't happen.
They had to work for it and they failed and they failed, and they failed, but they learned,
and they got back up, and they did it better.
Right.
All the lot of people we like here and their famous and all this didn't just happen over name.
Some people we other families, for our famous cardactions.
But I mean, like, a lot of other people, like, they had to work for it.
And they all, if you look at anyone, they do affirmations, they meditate,
they visualize all these people we look up to, do this shit.
It's the secret, the movie, the secret, the book, the secret.
Like, it's not a secret. Like, we have the power.
Because you can change your, because if you dive into a lot of those,
you know, the movie, the secret, like, even on YouTube, they have so many,
like, motivation ones, and they're so cool because when you start listening to that,
many, let it play and you just stay open to it.
It starts making so much sense. It really does.
It starts for me, because I used to, I would see those things and not know anything about them.
So I'd be like, I don't know what fuck a lot of traction does.
I'm gonna make sure they're not real.
Yeah, not that I would like disbelieve it, or, you know,
like totally just absolutely do my best to not believe it.
But I would just ignore it, because I'm like that, that I mean.
But when you just start learning about these things and listening to them and opening a
year's drum, a little bit, it's like, huh, it does help your beliefs.
But I wanted to read something because I kept going to this page.
I know I don't know how long, I don't know how time works, I don't know.
How much more time we want, or...
No, we're totally good as long as you want to get going.
So it's called Acceptance, and I went to this page yesterday.
This book is called The Little Book of Interpiece, and if you let go a little,
you will have a little piece.
If you let go a lot, you will have a lot of piece.
If you let go completely, you will have complete piece.
That is so mean. I have, I'm let go, let go, like, let go, like, I struggle with that.
A lot, and it's something I'm working on all the time.
That's like my mantra, like, let go, like I write it in a draw and I art, because it's like,
I don't know holding onto an emotion or holding onto the idea of how I wanted something to go,
because I'm a planner, and if it doesn't go my way, why is it crushing me?
Oh my gosh, yeah. I find that even when I'll DJ like a small bar,
and I'm like, oh, this isn't going, but it has to do this, it's just a small bar, and these people,
like, they're just having, they're totally fine. This isn't a detrimental, but you put it on yourself,
and you're like, I need to hold onto this shame or whatever comes at you.
Yeah, like I have said, like, my boyfriend's from Hawaii, so I'm like a time Nazi.
Like, I have an internal clock that's so on point. Like, it's 245, like,
any time of the day, and he's like, well, I don't know, maybe it's like, one or noon, and I'm like,
let's go, like, and he's always late, but really it's always on time if you change your perception,
because we always are on time. I'm like, oh, really, really, really, and then it always happens
so we show it right on time as we need it to. Maybe it's not 12 o'clock, 12 o'clock, like, people like,
but it's like, on time for the energy, on time for the traffic, on time for whatever,
and the more and more I'm letting go of my constant need to control time and getting the car at 10.
55, because we need to leave right now, because I map-quested it and it takes 23 minutes to get there with traffic.
It's like, whoa, like, let go. Like, it's okay to plan, but it's also like,
it's a control thing, and it's like that fear of the unknown, and like, just going with the flow,
sometimes is really hard for me. Yeah, because I think that a lot of times we, we misinterpret
what's really going on, because like, if you are rushing and you're irritated with yourself,
you're taking it with your partner, you're late to this thing now. Like, of course,
next time, like, try not to even let that be an option. If that's really that important to you,
but a lot of this, like, you show up, okay, you're on time, you're right on time, but you're
stressed out and you're not yourself. No, exactly. And you're talking too fast here, yeah.
And it, like, it feels me up, and to me, I took a so personal, like,
like, just, so what happened with me is we were sharing a car for a long time when he first got here,
and it was so hard to just let go of that. And like, I was learned, so I have abandoned my issues.
So what would happen after school is my mom would just sometimes not show up. So it's like that
sitting there on the sidewalk as a little kid, waiting for someone who's never going to come.
So what was happening is after work, he wasn't there. I got off different times, because I'm
a nurse, right? So you never know when you're done charting or when you're done with the last medicine
or last treatment, someone dies, you know, you never know what time you're done. So it's not like,
I'll be here at 5 o'clock every day. It's kind of like, I'm texting and calling you, this is what I'm off.
And, you know, he's not from here. So if he's in Vancouver, because he's exploring or like doing something,
and then I'm like, I'm done, he has to drive to come get me. Like, a logical person would
could say, okay, he's going to take 25 minutes, but that fear of no one showing up for me,
it was triggering me. Okay, right back up. And I was like screaming at him like, how can you be late? Like,
and it, but the thing is like, the card break down or he like, he had to help someone
inside of the road. There was all these things in the universe that kept making him late and he
can see it. He's like, until you heal from me being late, it's going to keep happening.
And it was, once I just like, accepted it, he was always on time and it never started,
but once, but it was triggering this inner child moment where I was like, my mom abandoned me,
and it was like, deep, heal, like a deep trauma that I didn't even realize I had of like,
she's just showing up for me, you know? And then like, something else I struggle with,
my relationship is, every time we would fight, I would just tell him to leave. Because in my mind,
the way I grew up, you, if you loved me left, because I'm how much go and leave. And to me,
that's all I was to show to love. You leave. So to me, it's like, why are you here? You obviously
don't love me because you're here. So we try to push people away because it's like, if you have
abandonment issues, it's like, leave. If you love me, you leave. Why are you here? Because it's
what love means to me. You need to make it to where it makes sense in my head. That's what I learned.
But it's like, now that you're here, you don't love me because you're here. And it's like, this
messed up twisted abandonment issues I had to rewire my brain. And he was like, what, he's
I'm not leaving. Like, what are you talking about? But I'm like being like a little child and
throwing tantrums. And it's like, who is this? I thought I was meditat. I was like, Zen and
a deep skull. And then I'm like screaming and crying. Like, I'm five, six, seven years old. Like,
it's just like uncontrollable. And he was like, well, it's so heavy. But it was like so healing because
a normal relationship, like, what the fuck is the world crazy and leaving? But he could see it as,
you have trauma to heal. And that's what we're doing for a child. And that's what we're doing for a child.
And pushed. Let's investigate. What is this? It's so cool that you're able to look at it,
you know, not only together and back where can we heal this. But just the fact that you're
able to say now, like, I don't want to act like that's not me. It's not like, because a lot of
times we feel so much shame behind our like outbursts, our like that we don't really want to deal with the
fact that like, man, I was acting out of line and I think maybe this is why. A lot of times we
want to like, well, of course, I was acting out of that. I had a bad day and you did this and you're
never on time and all these things, we and we think that that is like an answer like that's that's
justification in there. But it's yeah. There's so convenient. I mean, you've been in a relationship for
nine years. Yeah. So much communication. Oh my gosh, yeah, it's always improving. Yeah, it's always
true. It's always true. It's never ending. And I think another thing is we don't like to
hope talk about like, my friend and I fight, we fight. It's normal. It doesn't mean we're not in love.
But it's not like fighting where it's like we're being mean to each other and putting each other down.
Yeah. It's not that kind of like that's not right. That's weird. Yeah, when people are like, they're
like, here, I know something that you personally feel very uncomfortable about yourself. I'm going to throw
it at you. I know you. I see those kind of friends that fight like that. I'm like,
yeah, that's not right. That's that's, you know, that is there like it's very toxic. It's it's very toxic.
And I think just noticing like, okay, so if you're one of these people and that's happened to you
and your anger gets the best of you and whatever, like, if now right this conversation is like,
I'm trying to get into this. Yeah, and it does trigger something that's something that's being
pushed up on again. And you can now when this happens again, you're going to have this little
sliver I bet. That's going to be like, hmm, maybe I don't have to react like that. I'm queen of
talking about relationships. I think I love being in a relationship. It helps me grow. It's a mirror. I can
learn more about I love being in a relationship. It shows me where I need to grow. When you're by yourself,
you're like, yeah, yeah, but when you're living in a small quarter with someone, you're like,
woo, because really like the person you're wish should make you better or what's the point to me.
Right. The whole point of our relationship is to love and help each other grow and grow individually,
but together at the same time, kind of like a money tree like this. You know, and have the same
visions and encourage each other and like if your partner is in doing that for you, like I know
this sounds like shitty, but it's like, what's the point to me? In my relationship, if they're not
making you grow or pushing you or supporting you and all they're doing is thinking your ideas are
dumb and they're putting you down all the time, is that really like what you want? Because I know
so many women that are in shitty relationships with people who put them down. I hear some of the
things that these men say to my friends and I'm like, oh, yeah, someone you love the most is putting
you down the most, but oh, God. Do you think that a lot of people, like so,
we take the love you think you deserve, right? Oh yeah, that's a rough one too. That's definitely, I mean,
but these men, I just don't even know if they know they're doing it or they, I don't know.
I think a lot of it is, you know, not that it's okay. That doesn't matter if you make it okay,
but I think a lot of our, when we make fun of people and the things that we say in the, you know,
well, men being feminine too and expressing their feelings. Yeah.
Tabu. I mean, yeah, my whole life has definitely been, I've been, I've been beat up by Red
Next Growing Up, I've been, I've always been, so like in Kelso for as far as, as far as what I was
aware, I was probably too focused on myself, right, but like in high school, I was like, oh, I'm the first
guy to wear the tight pants. I'm the first guy to try red eyeliner and see if says anything.
I'm the first guy to dye my hair pink. You sort of think, like, I've probably wasn't really,
but, uh, you're mine. Right. But, but, but, what's it feminine? Yeah, but you see how other people react.
And they, and they hate it and they, and a lot of guys, like, uh, I say Red Next beat up by Red Next,
that's just a term that around here. A lot of people, uh, you know, drive a Toyota, work at a lumber
milling, you know, these sort of, um, personnel attached. But a lot of times, uh, I would notice
it's not so much that they're trying to, to make fun of me as much as it's like an unawareness that
they are making fun of me. And they don't really like the same. And they don't really like the same.
Scared that you can embrace your, like, a feminine energy. Oh, yeah, dude, when you see,
when you are an alpha male, and then an alpha male who's feminine walks into that room,
you feel very shivers. Yeah, it's weird. And it's crazy because like, same with females, like when
like, I remember when like girls were like, short skirts, and that triggered me, like, who are you,
you know, when I was like in high school, like, were you to like dress like that? But really,
she's just like, she's comfortable in her body. And she should be able to wear what she wants.
And it doesn't affect you. Yeah, why doesn't it? But it triggers you because you're not open,
like that to do it yourself. Yeah. For me, like, or, you know, people were getting ready all the time,
or, you know, I'm like, oh, like, that's, you know, I don't get it, but it doesn't mean that it
doesn't bother me. Like, I don't care. It's just not me. Right. But people who were like,
more feminine and like, like to do their eyelashes in their hair and their makeup, nothing's wrong with
that. But like, I was like, I just never been like that. But it doesn't matter. Yeah, you don't have a
opinion on it. Like, even if even if you do it every day. Yeah, you don't have to see other people
as wearing makeup or not wearing makeup. I don't even see that anymore. It's just them being them.
Yeah, I think we're like, the more you, the more you like meditate and the more you,
for me, it was definitely a staying wave from social media. You start to like realize that like
the things that you held onto, like your judgments about other people, they float away to where,
like, you don't even remember that you had them at some point. Like, you're just talking to someone
and then, I don't know, you wouldn't even notice something like if they're wearing it to
make it, you wouldn't notice that if you didn't force it. No, and I just think like, this area is super,
I don't know, but like, it's hot. I don't feel like a lot of people are truly stepping into their
authenticity and being themselves because we mask it with a lot of things. Because I feel like a lot
of us do the same things every day. We go to the, there's like two bars or, you know, there's not
a lot of do in this town or, you know, we do this, we have the same friend group forever. And I feel like
it's really uncomfortable for people to step out of that comfort zone and go explore and be by
themselves and like meeting people or move or it gets, it's where, I mean, I move, I'm why
I'm back. Like, something is here, you know, but I feel like I'm here to help people in the area
for some, I'm here for a reason. No, no. No, no. No, no. No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no. We're here in this
weird ass town for a reason, right? Yeah, it's funny because like, you know, you grow up and you have
your opinions in different places. Like, redneck, for example, that word would affiliate the town
that I live in now, Castle Rock, I would affiliate as a younger kid, this town with rednicks.
I don't know, there's rednicks living in there. And then you grow up and you, and you learn like,
oh, that's just, that's just a couple people that I saw to fill it at a whole town or that,
you know, and I think, you know, I, you know, traveling around for work and stuff throughout the
years, I was always, I wanted to get away from here. Like I was like, I want to move out
for the sunshine and now it's like, I just understand things differently and I'm like, I love it here.
And there's it's so interesting, like, right between Seattle and Portland and, and is there
in the ocean, the oceans and the mountain, the forest? Right, and I, just the places that you can
go, it's a spectacular place. Literally in the most perfect place. Like we can literally go to Portland.
We can go this like anywhere we want, it's cheap to fly out of Portland, like it's a best airport
in the country. Like, we just have so much around us. And I think we just, sometimes get stuck in our town.
On the other side, like, on one's the last time I left, like, woodland, it's been a week.
Like, sometimes you get stuck in, I need to go to Portland and reset and like feel like creative.
And we have so many different things that we can reset with here is, is this thing. Like, you can,
if you want to go to waterfall cool an hour away, if you want to go to the ocean cool an hour and 20 minutes away.
If you want to go to the mountain cool 45 minutes, it's all these things. I think instead of doing
the exact same things every weekend and keep doing these the same weekend and the same whatever
living and over, try to try to see what's around you. I mean, a lot of our listeners are probably
people that I know for the most part. And I just want to say that like, I love everyone that I've met.
Everyone that I partied with would do so much for have helped me so many times. And I see the creative
and I see the light and like, I think of Adrian right away. Like, I love Adrian. I love you.
If you're listening and like, I think of and always smiling like, I just think of so many people
and like Bailey Keakin. Like I just, there's so many people in this town that I just like love and they're just so full of light and just,
it's amazing how we all are here. And I feel like we're all here everywhere. Like there's a bunch of these towns that are like this.
It's just that lack of connection like we don't get to see each other in like a sober way.
That's why I want to create like a space where we can just like hang out and like talk.
Well, I think that we have like this cool potential for this thing because we know like the names that you just said.
Like we know a lot of times we know so many different names from the parting from the whatever like me for like it's a we party together for
reason. Yeah, we're all connected. And now it's like we have this thing where we can stay in touch. We don't have to like,
we can be friends throughout life. Like we've got 45 more years. Like I'm probably going to see again, you know,
and I can say how are you and you could say I'm good and in we you can say I used to live this life and that's how we met.
But now I live this different life and we're still friends and you compare your life to each other.
I just feel like so many people like we party with are like so fun and like creative and like I think of our house party.
Like we're other house parties like this. Like I don't know.
Think so. I think it's crazy. Think about like we we know this podcast. I thinking of guests that I want to have on.
It's like endless lists. I have so many cool people that I know.
That's what I'm saying. I listen to people.
For things I'm like oh my gosh. Like Betto doing it so big. Like I just want to say like inspires me daily.
And like I've always loved him. Always vibe with him. Like so happy and stoked for what he's doing.
Because he's such a catalyst in a story for our town. Like you can do it.
And I see his stories all over the country. Like when he was saying like whiny, I was like I see it.
Yeah. It's not even like he's planting the season. All our brains to be creative.
Yeah. I love what he's doing. Dude you want to do a story. He plants a seed for sure.
Yeah. All of his guys do. And it's just like that.
But it's in our town for a reason. Like we're just surrounded by these creative beings.
And not everyone stepped into it. Not everyone knows. But it's like nothing's random.
Like we all have this intercosmic soul family web where we are friends with all of each other.
And the web web web web web web. We know this person. No, this person's like we're all supposed to create this new world.
It's so it's now I'm the one getting chills.
I'm just kidding. I just keep getting it. It excites me to think like my I think a lot of it is.
It's rushing in of like thinking and giving myself a future because I had so many like I'm going to end
thing sort of thoughts for so many years that like I think of like okay here's my connections that I
know all these people like think about people just need about they're so awesome. And it's like oh yeah
in like going forward in life like we're going to have interactions and we're going to be able to build these
things together and it's very exciting. Yeah, we are so blessed like you know yeah there is like some
minor drama but like at the core like those people would be there for you. No doubt if you call them
like they would come at least I at least I believe in my heart. But I just feel like those genuine
like party connections like yeah we're all fucked up but there's a reason we kept partying together
all the time any house this house this house who's here you're here. I was at that party
house that I was like we were all at the same parties and it was like a reason we were all
and all of us probably had Toronto that's why we're drinking at 1340. No doubt the amount of
people that I mean the serious probably crying conversations that I've had just at parties sometimes
you just get a little drunk and you're talking with someone who just understands what you're saying
and you get into it. I mean did you grow up excuse me when you were like in high school did you
party in high school I did because I like it's super interesting I'm 28. I'm 24 so it was like
oh yeah but yeah still probably somewhere things like around here like you I don't know if it's
differently California if they party at the beach or something but we definitely go to like house
parties and it's you know a lot of the like the amount of the amount of the amount of
serious wonderful very smart conversations I've had at an outdoor glass table. Yeah
that outdoor glass table like in it's cool if you're kind of like that you know
you're going to glass table in here that's just a full of moldy but you know it's like those
girls that always have like the bathroom you know the bathroom line story the girls and
you people in the bathroom and they come best friends. It's so true though like I just feel like
that's why I'm at now but in a sober way in a way that I just want to like I want you to just
freaking go for your dreams like I just like go for it like anyone that's listening like just
go for it because like you can do anything you want and I just like well I see people
I'll question people I'll be at a gas station like what do you want to do for a living and they'll tell
me and I'm like why aren't you go for it and people don't get question enough question people in
your life what are you doing do you want to do this why don't you change yes in my father
them might trigger them I'm like do something yes why not how people did do something and be encouraging
and curing you want to be rude about it but like I'm like like up like I just want everyone to
see how beautiful they really are and like just see like how wonderful the world is and like
sometimes like it's gonna be hard to do when you're not feeling good or depressed but like just like
if you can do that for someone else and it can come back and like just be compassionate always
that's like my main thing is like be compassionate like I had to write down my five values the other
day and I was like compassion is like my number one injustice equality love and empathy so it's like
what are your five values and are you embodying those every single day I think a lot I think a lot
of people don't even ask what their values are I mean I didn't for very long time you need to tell more
until you know again like two years ago and now it's like my life is better like knowing that I you
know maybe I'm still circling some of them I think but I think like solidifying them and allowing
myself to have them so you know I think it's just hard to be human but there's people around you that
are going through the same thing and probably your neighbor literally right you think they're you think
they're judging you for where and but you have a pants outside they're just going through their own
shit too yeah and like I think to take things like lighter and to just be more kind and gentle
with yourself and to not be so hard on yourself because I'm so hard on myself I right to do this
every day and I put 50 things on it and I do four and I'm like oh man my day sucks but really it's like
it didn't right I just have these high expectations and then when I don't meet them I like him down
and I'm like but I did something I wasn't just sitting all day and it's like but I but I
felt like I wasn't doing anything and I really reflect and I'm like what did I do you know but I
wasn't just doing nothing so it's like you're working towards it you see yourself as this
higher like I know that I am capable one day or you know something like I'm gonna do these things
I'm gonna get all 12 things done but I did do four today and that's so great you know like give it
the reflect is a great word I think a lot of people a lot of times we have so much momentum so much
forward movement in our lives that we don't give ourselves time to reflect like yeah I'm not maybe I'm
not living my dream right this day but like I did good today and that's that's cool like give
yourself like oh like you know for example and think the crazy thing is it's like I've been enrolled
in herbal school for like almost a year but I can't I have not done it why am I holding myself back
it's almost like I am scared to step into my late so like I'm I don't feel deserving to be
my dream job so that's where the deserving comes in so it's like yeah I took that step and I'm
paying for it every single month but why am I not taking the time to do it for myself and it
all stems from the lack of I don't deserve to do this or I'm not gonna make enough money or what
do I know or I'm not good enough and it's crazy because it's like this constant battle or herbal
schools on my to do list every single day but it's like I'm not doing it and that's like I'm just
need to do it and I was like we went to the hot springs the other day and I'm like I want to go
to an after-pad at school and my friends like you're not even doing the school you have now
he's like why are you like trying to add things to your plate add things to your plate add things
to your plate and then you're not even doing the things that are on your plate it becomes too much
you have too many options but I like being like that so weird it's novelty I think it's I sometimes I
feel like I'm so fascinated by fucking everything but I just like the professional and all the areas
of it that I can yeah but like my biggest thing like my biggest goals are to do like a blog and
like having YouTube channel I don't know like what is exactly what I just know that I need to speak
I know like with my Instagram like it's social media and like when I quit doing it like
because like you struggle to like with your mind and social media but to me it's like I get off and
I'm like oh I feel good but then it's like I need to speak because my videos people are like thank
you I need to do fear this I'm feeling the same way I can't tell you how many times I
do videos and people are like from all of the I have someone from Bulgaria that I've met New Zealand
Australia like all over South Africa women from all over the world finding me and they're like
I feel you 100% thank you and like how do they find you like whatever happened there I have to
stumble upon you so seriously these women I'm like and they're going through the same thing
they're feeling like I feel you all the way from here like Bulgaria I'm Bulgaria and it's like
what and she's like I feel like we're sisters like and it's so crazy because I'm talking to
these women and I have so much in common with them in their across the world but it's a collective shift
and people are tuning into it and that's how I feel like my Instagram is like a tuning into like my
show yeah I think you're you know of course do if you fill yourself drawn into it like take a step back
but I think your Instagram is great you should definitely keep going um I also we can talk about this
afterwards too so that's my plan I have a YouTube channel and I have the podcast uploaded I eventually
want to have video episodes that'll add to it but I also have a few like sometimes I'll have
pretty clear thoughts while I'm out hiking or something and I'm like I'm gonna try to talk to
the camera for 10 minutes you know so I have a couple of those up there but my plan I actually
would like to start making like a weekly blog or monthly blog something writing myself so we should
maybe try to fuel each other on that maybe text each other every few weeks and be like hey I do
it on that we should wait it's crazy because it's like a collective shift I'll get these crazy ideas and
thoughts I just download into my brain and I'll talk to a partner and he's like same so it's crazy
like I'm vegetarian and um yesterday I ate meat it's just so weird I was ashamed I was like
cause I haven't eaten me I'm like it's been like I've been vegetarian for like three years
I've like but yesterday I just like I don't know why but like this piece of sausage like looks
so good I'm like what the hell like I love it I'm also I'm like and then I talked to my boyfriend
I'm like I have a confession and he's like what I'm like I had a piece of sausage like that's
so weird I had a chicken sandwich yesterday he's vegetarian too and I'm like what I'm like it's
I wonder about that like what is that you know like I don't know he's like I didn't feel good
I only have blah blah blah I'm like he's like the only thing there was and I'm like whatever
really like there was more food but it's so weird and it's just um I think when we label ourselves
we get feel ashamed like I'm vegetarian and I eat an animal like I'm a bad person it's like
we make mistakes but it's like I obviously like I must be alone I earn or something or maybe
I'm not getting all what I need maybe just a reminder of why don't eat me because it doesn't
make me feel good or you know sometimes we need those slip-ups to be reminded of why we're doing it in
the first place right yeah okay so I want to just to be conscious of your time I want to
because you're talking about eating healthy um I feel like you have a bit of it yeah I feel like you
have some great advice so I just let's just take the you know last 15 minutes or so here and let's just
talk about you being an herbalist and talk about it yeah I just want to I feel like you have knowledge
in the outdoors and I'm so I'm very intrigued by um obviously anything diet wise or like how
the things that's going to the body as far as nature but I'm just very much I haven't fully
mix you can we tell you why I'm vegetarian because I was yeah yeah let's let's do that yes so
it all started when I was at summer camp I'm like I'm just going to tell everyone I'm vegetarian
even though I wasn't but I'm prideful right so it's crazy because 20 of the camp counts
for vegetarian so it was just like a vibe and I was like I was going to say for a vegetarian and once I
say that I'm prideful I'm not going to eat meat so that's how I was able to fully stick to it
if I was living on my own I don't know how I would have transformed into me not eating meat but since
I was placed in a camp situation where I wasn't able to choose my food but everyone else was looking
at what I was eating because I said as vegetarian so that's how I was able to fully embody like not eating
meat and moved to Hawaii and ate fish so I haven't been full of this pescaterian but I don't
really fish anymore but the reason I really really chose to stop is because I look at a pig or
chicken or a cow with the same love that I do when I look at my partner because it's their
their life and they have to me I feel their energy and their soul and their heart beating and like
I don't know like I don't feel like I'm any better than animals or bugs I've never killed a bug like
this is just me I'm very empathetic and I just I have dreams of like factory farms and like
I just you know growing up around cows like I pet you know I just couldn't imagine like killing
and like I see them on the on the trucks and I cry and I'm like personally I couldn't
kill an animal so I feel like I don't deserve to eat it for me while what's happening is I would
be eating a hamburger and I was sad I was starting to cry and I asked one of my spiritual teachers
was going on and she's like well you're taking on the fear of that animal so think about how
scared these animals are when they're dying right and then think about the people killing the
animals they don't like what they're doing most part they're happy and happy with their job
they're usually immigrants and they're low energy people killing the animal and think
how long the animal's been dead so you're eating like dead flesh and it just freaked me out
and all the bugs in it and then then the colors in it and then how long has it been dead
and you can watch any videos that'll just definitely yeah and nothing and that's another
amount of people that's like vegan or die like I don't want I don't believe in pushing and on
people it's super like I believe in the blood type thing too which is a different thing but I just
felt in my heart that I could do it without animals and I just felt like I loved animals so much and
when I look at my cats like other countries eat cats and like how could they eat a cat how could they
eat a dog and it's like we everything right it's just different it's it's so weird I think that
we're so disconnected from well like I always talk about like we nuggets you know you're eating a chicken
you know we change the names of the food it we're eating pepperoni, reading slimy what animal
animal eating I don't know what I'm eating like meat love like what is like you know we're
not really taught we're not associated so we as children we don't associate the meat with the animal
we're eating we'll change it into something else because I guarantee like I told they I'm like
if we have kid they want to eat meat they have to kill it themselves and if they can't kill it
they don't get it maybe that's crazy but I'm like because if you gave me that option to do this for
some savage who's out there just hunt those little things we're gonna grow a social path
he's like five just dead I brought him this deer love he drove that we talked about that too
but I just feel like I can't kill it so I don't deserve to eat it and I so empathetic in my
power is just grow daily that I was literally feeling the fear of these animals in my body
and I was scared and my anxiety was bad and I I have friends who are vegetarian and they go
back to eating me and they're anxiety gets bad and I also think about energy right so
if you think that you're eating something that literally was alive and it's been dead so you're eating
something that's dead and you want to feel alive explain that to me and so something else that's
really interesting is so stakes it's in your stomach for three days so imagine like a 98 degree hot
went um Washington day and you throw a stake on the sidewalk how would it look and smell and feel
well that's what's happening inside your stomach and then it take you think our intestines are
really long like football field long and then this piece of meat is like dragging along and you're
testing and it's like cutting off and it's breaking off and it stays in there and we don't digest it
very well um animals who eat meat their intestines are way shorter than ours like way shorter like
feet like six ten feet shorter than ours the way they absorb things so they have to eat me and they eat
it raw too they don't cook you don't see cheetahs like cooking their meat on like a stove like
we don't eat it raw I'm just really into the raw thing where I feel better when I vegetable is
in fruit I feel more alive like the vibration like I can I like sampling gradients so I like to
think like who found my food the energy of my farmer like was it a happy farmer like what do we
or is it someone at McDonald's who hates their life and they're putting hate into your food
and then you're putting the energy into your body I totally feel that because I think the same way
yeah I think that there's more you know when you so say you go to like a farmer's market down
the road from your house or something like you have this interaction with this person you can
see who you're food it's so crazy you tell you about it and I call you I'm like you know my family's
own a honey farm for my whole life and there's money and whatever and it's kind of what you're
leaning towards crazy. One of me my family or farmers you know so-called nursery is a
out of farms like that's how we started but it's also just like being connected to your food I
am very passionate about that like where's your food come oh I get so crazy like when my
QE's are from New Zealand like how long ago was that picked and then the process of getting here
and just like I one day I want to like that's why I love to why so much because I'm eating like
off the trees and it just feels so right but when we're eating food that's been picked or
dead for a while and it's hard to feel good with your food right you know we're so disconnected
from our food and I'm so yeah I think in other times people don't realize how draining their
food is because they don't really aren't in tune with their body oh man but like this morning
my boyfriend brought home because he sometimes not very good he brought home like had a love
potatoes he brought home a hash brown and I ate it and I instantly felt sick and I had to go
meditate and like do a taro and like I went and bought a juice to like make up for it because I like
felt like greasy and like low energy and like I don't eat like Donald like I don't like Donald's
like why did I do that you know yeah I think exploring what your body feels like so when you first
started when you're like okay like this is obviously affecting me eating this meat when you started
switching to just just whatever you went to what was that like do you remember those first couple
months was like this is hard because like I like quick fast food like I used to freaking go to
talk about McDonald's and one drive through setting like yeah I like ate talk of it
today I just like get no cheese or meat like not much the best but I just feel like I mean it's a
vibe like another thing I want to care like stress is consumers control like sensors all the milk
the dairy consumption has gone down so much like dairy farms are getting shut down all over the
country because we don't need it as much because consumers control it so it's like another thing I'm
really passionate about is we're cutting down acres of the Amazon to graze more cow so that's another
thing it's the environment and then I also think how many gallons of fresh water are we wasting
on these livestock we yeah the fresh water crisis don't even get me started on well also soil only has
so many year like you can't if you just keep digging up the same farm every year well that's why
they have to keep grazing and cutting down more and more forest old forest forest that has been
there longer than we can think to graze more animals for a temporary satisfaction just isn't
doesn't vibe with me and for what I like when I wrote up my mission goal and like my life
statement my purpose and why I'm here it's to save the planet so to me saving the planet
starts with what I put into my body and consumer and you know once I started going vegan I was like
oh my god there's feathers in my blanket how they get here in my mongles they pluck them from ducks
alive and I just think about like we don't think about it and we disconnect ourselves from those things
yeah and I just like oh my god I was like I wanted and like there's leather and like everything and
like I just what was happening though is I was getting so crazy like every we were on a road trip
and I was like in Vegas and I was like crying because of just like you can see the consumption
and like the resources and I'm just like people just don't see it and it's not their fault but
like I like to you're thinking about it it's just like we are draining the earth so hard and all she does is like
love us right I think that the the important thing though is is you see it and other people's don't
and that's not so much of like they're all bad it's like I see it so like I got to guess teach them
you know and this will seems to be your dealing I mean like if you think of like indigenous people they
worship the ground they stomped on the ground they worship the sun they pray to the water like
do you do you have speaking of I just want to touch them that good but you probably have good
I'm big on grounding for me it's like so when I get off a plane I get home and I'm like I go
on the bat of course I love to have a joint of comfort with it but take off my shoes and then
stomped around all if I feel like doing yoga and just rolling around in my grassman
you know the science behind that yeah I do a little bit but I love you to to
so the way that works is you there's free ions in the earth energy on the ground and it's a
flick of there's abundant amounts so when you are on balance there's something the free ions
literally you have shockers on the bottom of your feet and sometimes they can get clogged or
not ground when you start to walk on the grass they start to open up and then these free ions
literally enter through the bottom of your feet and ground you and connect you you'll notice
you're grounded people who can't stand on both feet or like kind of on one foot other foot
like me like you're not both feet on the ground means you're on grounded you can see that
all the time if you're leaning one way or leaning the other or your feet don't touch the ground
or you're on grounded and it being grounded is something I'm working on every day because I'm
really on grounded right okay so what's your technique for for a grounding mine is definitely
just walking down like well like same thing like definitely walking outside definitely like
grounding meditation so like an easy way to ground is like think of a root coming from like
the bottom of your like sit bone and like put it deep into the earth and it just everything like
releases and releases and releases and releases and then take up earth energy and bring it up
you know out through your head connect with the sky and then bring it back and create like this
chronic like in and out influx of energy yeah yeah it's like one continuous thing even though you
can't see it like you can vision it and it's happening you know people like oh I want like I don't
see or I have a lot of friends who see or is and that's their gift I have different gifts you know
I want to see it where I want to see energy just because you can't see it doesn't mean it's not
there you know I think of dogs here sound we don't hear it isn't me the sound isn't there
we just can't hear it because we're not on that frequency same with energy so same thing
and I think I think a lot of visualization tunes us into you know almost like a tricking of your
brain like a lot for me a lot of feeling these things and like connecting with them is following
kind of meditations and like in so so so got a meditations for example they'll tell me that I just
recently said something you did imagine a root coming from you know your your root chakra here
your but rather you push it through the ground and through these things like through the meditation
I follow I give into it I I they say envision your roots going through the ground and feel it
dirty and you feel that and you say what what would it be like in my head what would it be like right now
if I did have roots coming out of my body and just grab the energy yeah well I know and that's
you know you lie yourself with feeling it's very it's profoundly healing you know a lot of these
I don't know I I always just think of like that person who sits down and they hear that like imagine a
a root going through the ground the person like what the fuck are you talking about you just I always like
bringing that up because I used to be one of those people I feel like yeah and other things sorry
no we're like getting close but like those of you who say you can't meditate or the ones who need to meditate
the most I'm so I love yeah I repeat that again those who say they can't meditate or the ones who
need to meditate the most what advice do you have for those people I think that when you start
you're gonna hear a lot of thoughts and it's okay you don't have to be an expert like when I first
started I literally was like no turn off I can't sit still with my thoughts but I can be on my
phone for hours mindlessly I started with headspace it's a great free app there's a 10 minute guided
one and just I also recommend doing the same meditation every day so because you start to get ready for
the words and the music sounds the same and like it's like a two minute one is on YouTube and what
you learn is you start to listen to it and your brain is a muscle and you're training it so you hear
that music and you're like I know what to do time to relax and you grow and you grow and you grow
and you grow and you grow and eventually you can do it longer and you do it longer and it just happens
it doesn't happen overnight yeah you can you can I'm gonna do an hour meditation today no if you
don't meditate please don't do that because you're just gonna get frustrated and fail yeah you're
gonna see it as this giant staircase you know I'm gonna want to take another step tomorrow there's
literally like I have a Facebook group I created called Love and Light and I'm just like literally
here's a two minute meditation you can do it when you get home from driving from work that's enough to
reset you I mean you could fill two minutes two minutes of closing your eyes and connecting with
something that feels real and feels soft and comfortable and if you don't like people talking
at you I listen to whale sounds a lot tell you yeah whale sounds I'm all down for whale sounds or
like the Amazon rainforest or like anything like natural doesn't always have to be guided you know
if you just need to be sit they can listen to like nature sounds or something whatever like floats your
boat or if it's like instrumental I also love like moza and like piano and like that kind of stuff
too so it's whatever like you can do to quiet it yeah we totally listen to a lot of the same stuff
because I like a week ago I was listening to whale sounds for a while yeah really what the hell
my is it's an option on Spotify how can you not click on it I was like I saw I like what
do whales a lot so I just think yeah I don't think that I do yeah do you about being underwater
a lot I think breathing underwater like I'm like living in the ocean a lot really I so I actually
have a it's weird I don't know if it's fear so I have a little bit of fear of water uh yeah
me too I think I had a moment I think I had like a traumatizing experience like two minute
meditation right hey maybe that's what it was but I do I feel also a drawing a connection to water
I feel like I'm past love water really yeah okay because when I go so cold water lake for
examples of my favorite places um is and you know when I read yesterday actually I had no idea
it wasn't there before 1980 when the volcano yeah it's a new lake yeah I had no idea but I
feel very you go there and there's a scare but there's also this like connection to the water
it's a little scary and dark but but your fears are like I have the fear of like I'm in lagoon
and something's gonna pull me down and like yeah that's irrational but I feel like it like oh
like let's down there you know you're like so faster and it's like what is that it's irrational
and you just like when you let go you can enjoy yourself so I always wonder like how many times
fear has held people back from like having these amazing experiences like jump off that cliff
no I'm scared but when you jump you feel so good after when you're in the water yes fear is it
everything that you love everything you love everything that's you is on the other side of fear it's
yeah it's it's a constant battle but like you should jump off a lot of cliffs but no but you know what I mean
like fear like has been holding me back from like reaching my full potential and I think for me like
it's truly scary to like step into the light because a lot of people aren't there or doing it and
who am I in 24 year old like from the small town but we are like magnificent beings and like we all
have this and I say it's just everyone's at different stages of it absolutely I mean I think you're
magnificent and I feel like being able to like the fact that I had no you and I can have you on my podcast
and this is like what's creating itself and it's it's just a wonderful thing thank you for having
me I appreciate it and like just creating this space to have like conversations and I feel like your
intentions are so pure and it really like shines through and I think that's why your the
glissaners are growing because I can like feel it you don't have like this interior mode of
to make all this money which is nothing wrong with that but I can feel like your intentions like
shine through and the listeners can like feel that it's like for them you know but for you with the
same time it's like to have people at the same time it is and honestly it feels it's it's very
fulfilling and it just feels right like I don't know much more than I just feels super right and it feels
feels good I enjoy doing it and and I I know whatever is going to come from it is going to be
what I need to do you know it's just it's just so obvious so let's just round about shout out your
Instagram let's let's make sure everyone knows where to find you you're a wonderful person if I want
to Instagram that's what's written in the future let's also work on YouTube channel more stuff we can
even have more podcast episodes that would be great yeah I would love to it's a less dual gypsy witch
but I guess we can probably close it on your page underneath there's something definitely but yeah
I feel just super honored to be here but I just really want if you're still listening to this like
to realize like you are here for a reason and I think you aren't probably told that enough I really
feel like that people aren't told that enough that you are here for a reason and you are needed and you are
loved you are needed you are loved and you are here for a reason listen absolutely agree with you
it was such a great conversation yeah thank you so much thank you have a good rest of your day
listen there's drinks and water take care of yourself